Prologue: An Unexpected Encounter

On the western side of the Galarc Kingdom, on a road running through the forest to the west of Amande...

After the battle with the army of monsters that had attacked Liselotte’s party had ended, Princess Flora was left staring at Rio’s face in a daze.

Oh dear... A troubled expression fell over Rio’s face as he received Flora’s gaze.

And there was good reason for it: Rio had disappeared before, after he was falsely accused of a crime by the nobility of the Beltrum Kingdom. It wasn’t as though Flora herself had framed Rio for the crime, but he had hoped to never see the royalty and nobility of that kingdom again, including Flora herself.

It’s been years since I last saw Princess Flora. I’ve gone through my growth period since then. My hair is also a different color thanks to this artifact, so even if she suspects me, I just have to feign ignorance.

Rio did not lose his cool. He decided to maintain the air of confusion he was putting on in reaction to the staring from a member of royalty, tilting his head in question.

“...Is something the matter, Princess Flora?” Liselotte asked Flora curiously. Beside her, Duke Huguenot was also watching Flora with a suspicious look on his face.

When Flora realized everyone’s attention had been focused on her, she shook her head in a fluster. “Huh? Ah, no, it’s nothing!” Despite this, she continued to look inquiringly in Rio’s direction.

At this point, even Liselotte and Duke Huguenot started to suspect that that her odd behavior must have had something to do with Rio. The two of them looked at him.

Rio decided to speak up first, placing his right hand over his chest respectfully as he sank to one knee. “...Forgive me for asking, but have I possibly committed something of great offense? If so, please allow me to offer my most humble apologies...”

“N-No, you haven’t! That’s not it! It’s not like that, no! It’s — It’s nothing of the sort, just...” Flora denied in shock, struggling to find her words as she trailed off.

Everyone present waited for her to continue her statement. After a pause, Flora opened her mouth fearfully. “Umm, I was just wondering if we’ve met somewhere before.”

“...Me, Your Highness? I cannot say I recall such a moment, perhaps you have mistaken me for someone else?” Rio made a show of surprise and played dumb, sounding as genuine as possible.

“Oh, I see...” Flora frowned in frustration.

“...Hmm. Are you nobility from a kingdom somewhere?” Duke Huguenot suddenly asked, his words directed at Rio. He was curious about Rio’s background, having been informed of nothing but his name. Based on Flora’s statement, he assumed that Rio was nobility from somewhere, and so he tried to discern more with his question. If that were the case, then it wouldn’t be strange for Rio and Flora to have met before.

“No, I am merely a traveler, wandering through the lands on a pilgrimage to train my sword hand. I am not someone born high enough to ever dream of being in the presence of royalty.” Rio shook his head with a bittersweet smile.

“Oh? A swordsman of this skill, living secluded without any affiliation to a kingdom...” Duke Huguenot hummed with deep interest. “Ah, excuse me. As Liselotte introduced earlier, I am Gustav Huguenot, just another old and useless noble.”

“Even my estranged self has heard word of the great Duke Huguenot family before. It is an honor to be in your presence.”

“Hahaha, I am most humbled to hear that.”

“And I am too, for your most favorable evaluation of my unworthy skills.” Rio and Duke Huguenot exchanged words in a friendly show of humility.

So this is that Stewart Huguenot’s father... He sure seems like a typical shrewd noble, Rio analyzed.

The Huguenot family was the one he had the deepest connection to out of all the high nobility in Beltrum. Several years ago, there was an incident where Flora nearly fell off a cliff during an outdoor drill. Though he hadn’t confirmed this for certain, Rio was fairly sure that Duke Huguenot was the one to place the false accusation on his head. Not to mention the fact he was also the main culprit behind Latifa’s enslavement...

However, for some strange reason, Rio didn’t feel any hatred toward his near-fated enemy, who now stood right before him. Of course, that didn’t mean he wanted to get involved with him more than necessary — Rio was simply willing to use him if needed, then discard him without a care after. Rio had a different goal elsewhere, after all.

But Princess Flora and Duke Huguenot don’t matter right now. Liselotte Cretia is what’s important. That’s right — Rio’s true target was Liselotte.

There were two reasons for it: first, she was the daughter of Duke Cretia, the widely known lord of Galarc. Second, as president, she was the key figure of the Ricca Guild, famous across all the nearby lands.

It was definitely a wise choice to form a favorable relationship with Liselotte, just in case either of Miharu’s friends — Sendou Takahisa or Sumeragi Satsuki — had been summoned in the royal castle of Galarc as heroes. If things went well, she could be the bridge that connected him to them.

In that regard, while saving Celia’s old friend Aria during their earlier battle was more of an indirect goal, it had also been a once-in-a-lifetime chance to befriend Liselotte. Although the undesired encounter with certain figures had been a little unexpected...

In the end, making contact with noble society would have opened the door to possible encounters with people from Beltrum later anyway — it had just happened now instead.

With the friendly smile still on his face, Rio repeated those words to himself. He had to reset his feelings and believe that this was his first time meeting Flora and Duke Huguenot.

“Umm, I should have introduced myself earlier. My name is Flora Beltrum. Thank you very much for saving us from that dangerous situation earlier.” Flora eyed Rio’s expression carefully as she thanked him with nervous diffidence.

Rio shook his head gently. “It was nothing. I’m glad to have been of help.”

At that point, Hiroaki made his belated grand appearance with Roanna in tow. “Ah... Hey. Who is this guy, exactly? Someone you all know?”

When Rio spotted Hiroaki, his eyes widened faintly. He heard Flora quietly mumble the word “hero” and immediately knew who this boy was.

...He’s younger than I expected. I believe they said his name was Hiroaki Sakata? Rio thought, recalling the name he had found out when he snuck into the estate in Rodania.

“This is Sir Haruto. He is not acquainted with any of us, but he saved us and now we are in the middle of thanking him.” Liselotte said, taking the initiative to introduce Rio to Hiroaki.

“My honor to make your acquaintance.” Rio introduced himself, placing his right hand over his chest respectfully with a light bow. In the Strahl region, this was a formal pose that showed more respect than a bow to the other person. It wasn’t a gesture that an uneducated person would use naturally.

When Liselotte and Duke Huguenot observed this conduct coupled with Rio’s courteous manner of speech, they felt even more certain that Rio was no ordinary commoner.

Meanwhile, Hiroaki was looking Rio up and down as though to evaluate his worth. “Hmm... I see. Oh, I should introduce myself. I’m Hiroaki Sakata. The hero, technically. It’s nice to meet you,” he said with a small shrug.

“...I had heard rumors that a hero had been summoned, but I never imagined it to be true,” Rio said, feigning surprise.

“Well, it’s a little hard to believe, yeah. But I’m the real deal.”

“No, I would never dare deny that. It is quite an honor to be meeting you in person.”

“Really, now. Well, there’s no need to prostrate yourself in return. You seem to be quite the swordsman yourself. I saw some of your fight just now,” Hiroaki said cheerfully, apparently satisfied with the self-deprecating attitude Rio was taking on.

“You are much too kind. However, if the great hero was present, then my assistance may have been unnecessary. I apologize for stepping out of line.” Rio bowed his head solemnly.

“Hm? Ah... Well, yeah. Honestly, my hero ability is far too powerful for this kind of scuffle. Of course, it’s not that I can’t cross swords face-to-face with anyone...” Hiroaki said vaguely, a somewhat awkward look on his face. Even he was feeling some sense of inferiority at his complete lack of participation in the earlier battle, but it didn’t seem like he was willing to admit that honestly.

“Forgive my forwardness, but Sir Hiroaki’s power is far too great. On such a small battlefield like earlier, it would have been difficult for him to moderate that power.” Roanna said, immediately supporting Hiroaki’s words.

Hiroaki nodded along. “Yeah, that’s right. That’s exactly right. One strike with all my might is pretty much the equivalent of a map wipeout. Oh, I should introduce you, too. This is Roanna, the daughter of Duke Fontaine.”

“I’m Roanna Fontaine. It’s a pleasure to meet you.” Roanna held the hem of her skirt daintily as she gave a graceful bow. The girl who had been Rio’s former classmate didn’t show any particular signs of suspicion towards him.

“It is nice to meet you, Lady Roanna. I am Haruto.” Deeming his disguise to be effective, Rio placed his right hand over his chest and greeted Roanna respectfully, then bowed to Liselotte’s party around him with a faint, uncomfortable smile. “With everyone being of such high status, I’m starting to feel a little nervous in all your great presences.”

“Oh, my. In the earlier battle, you stood against that minotaur with no fear at all, did you not? How could someone so bold before a monster so huge ever be nervous?” Liselotte giggled in amusement.

“Yes, that is true. The way you handled the earlier fight was splendid,” Roanna agreed with a giggle.

“Yes, it was like the fight of a hero from legend,” Flora said, nodding along.

“Hahaha, even I must admit the fight just now had my heart leaping in this old, weary chest of mine.” Even Duke Huguenot echoed the opinions of the girls.

Hiroaki cleared his throat quietly. “Ah, ahem. Let’s not keep standing around idly any longer. Our horse and carriage was blown away somewhere, should we move to the unharmed carriage instead?” he suggested, cutting the flow of the conversation.

“In that case, allow me to assist the others. It seems you could do with a helping hand,” Rio offered.

“Lady Liselotte, do you have a moment to listen to a quick report?” Chloe suddenly said as she approached them timidly.

“What’s the matter?”

“What shall we do about the carriage that was blown away by the monster? We were fortunately able to heal the horses that were sent flying alongside it, but the heavy damage to the roof and wheels makes moving the carriage a difficulty. We also lack the craftsmen to make any emergency repairs...” Chloe explained with a troubled look.

“I see. I wanted to use it for transporting the injured if possible, but...” Liselotte pondered worriedly. If she had been the only noble present right now, she would have immediately decided to give the remaining carriage to transport the wounded. But she couldn’t do that with Hiroaki and Flora here. In terms of status, it was impossible for her to ask them to walk.

“Repairs may be possible depending on how bad of a condition it’s in. By your leave, I could take a look at it,” Rio offered. He had learned much of his do-it-yourself carpentry skills from the dwarves of the spirit folk village.

Liselotte’s eyes widened. “Why, that would be a great help. If you don’t mind, Sir Haruto, I would love to take you up on that.”

Rio nodded readily. “It would be my pleasure. But I cannot guarantee I can fix it.”

“...Haru...to?” Chloe murmured in surprise, staring at Rio’s face.

“Hmm?” Rio tilted his head curiously.

“Chloe, stop. I apologize for my subordinate’s rudeness, Sir Haruto.”

“P-Please forgive me! You just had the same name as someone else I once met in the past.” Chloe immediately paled and apologized to Rio in a fluster.

Rio shook his head with a restless look. “No, I do not mind... May I ask where it was that you met that person?”

The number of people from the Strahl region that knew Rio’s alias of Haruto was extremely limited. On top of that, he recognized Chloe’s name too. But no matter how hard he tried, he couldn’t seem to remember.

“Answer him immediately,” Liselotte sighed. Chloe peered at Rio’s face as she questioned him fearfully.

“U-Umm, several years ago, at an inn in Amande... Did you, ah, have you ever stayed anywhere near there before? That inn was my family home, and I used to work there...”

Rio had only stopped by Amande once, several years ago: it was when he had run away from the kingdom of Beltrum with the false accusation on his head, on his way towards the Yagumo region. And there was only one inn he had stopped in at that time, all those years ago in Amande.

“...Ah, from that time.” Rio immediately connected his memories and widened his eyes in understanding. At the time, some drunk adventurers had picked a fight with him at the inn, so the memories still remained in his mind. But he had also encountered Latifa the next morning, so it was possible that was the clearer memory that endured...

“I-I knew it! You remember me!” With the truth confirmed, Chloe drew closer to Rio enthusiastically.

“Y-Yes, I believe you were calling out to potential customers on the streets?” Rio was slightly taken aback by the sudden difference in enthusiasm. Chloe nodded in excitement.

“Yes!”

I’m surprised she remembers. I remember hiding my face with my hood back then... right? That means this girl remembered me by just hearing my name, Rio thought in awe as he looked at Chloe.

Unless they left a deep impression on you, it should have been a fairly difficult feat to remember the name and face of someone you only met once several years ago. But Chloe’s mind had immediately jumped to Rio when she heard the name Haruto. She must have had quite the memory.

“Umm, you only stayed for one night back then, leaving right away in the morning...” Chloe spoke hesitantly.

“Yes, I believe I was in a hurry back then.” Rio replied, looking back on his memories.

Ah, come to think of it... Suddenly realizing something, he looked at Liselotte. Back then, he had also bought pasta, grains, and other ingredients for his journey from the Ricca Guild. The girl who had welcomed him during that time seemed to bear a resemblance to Liselotte. Their hair color was the same, and their faces were similar.

Liselotte had been staring at Rio, so when their gazes met, her eyes widened. “Did you two really know each other?”

“Yes. My apologies... I became too engrossed in the conversation.” Rio apologized immediately to Liselotte and the others. Though the conversation had led him that way, it was definitely not a preferable choice to leave royalty and nobility out.

“No no, please don’t mind us.”

“Indeed, we have witnessed a very interesting scene thanks to you.” Liselotte and Duke Huguenot brushed off the apology easily. Having gained an information source in the form of Chloe, they were much more willing to set aside their investigation of Rio’s background for now.

“You are all too kind,” Rio said, bowing lightly.

“...Am I really mistaken, then?” Flora muttered to herself as she examined Rio’s face.

Hiroaki noticed Flora’s muttering and looked towards her. “Ah, did you say something, Flora?”

“N-No, it’s nothing.” She shook her head in a fluster.

“...Then I shall go and confirm the state of the broken carriage now.” Rio decided to head towards the carriage before the conversation could drag out any further.

“I shall accompany you. Hero, you should relax in the carriage with the others,” Liselotte immediately offered.

“Ah, well, I guess there’s nothing I could do anyway. Let’s go, Flora, Roanna,” Hiroaki responded right away, walking off without waiting for their reply.

“Yes, Sir Hiroaki.” Roanna immediately followed Hiroaki’s retreating figure.

“Umm, please let me hear more about you later.” Flora looked like she wanted to continue talking to Rio, but with a glance at Hiroaki walking away, she had no choice but to follow. With a quick bow, she turned on her heel and hurried off.

“Hmm. Then I shall check on the status of the knights. I shall leave that side to you.” Duke Huguenot left with those words, heading for the knights of Beltrum Kingdom.

“Then, if you would please, Sir Haruto. Aria, Chloe. We’re going.” Liselotte bowed at Rio before calling to Aria and Chloe beside her. The two of them responded with a respectful “Yes, my lady.”

Thus, Rio made his way to the broken carriage accompanied by Liselotte and her attendants.

Chapter 1: The Road to Amande

After that, the group made their way to the broken horse carriage.

The carriage had been blown into the forests on the side of the road, completely overturned upon itself. Furthermore, the iron plating on the roof had been completely dented by the stone great sword, while several detached parts — including the wheels — lay around the surrounding area. It made the entire scene look like a wreckage.

There were two horses that had been sent flying along with the carriage, but the attendants had already used healing magic to treat them and had led them back to the main road.

Liselotte gazed upon the ruins with an uncomfortable expression. “How... does it look?” she asked Rio. To her amateur eye, it looked damaged beyond repair.

“...I may be able to do something about this.” Rio replied as he looked around at the scattered parts of the carriage.

“Right... of course. Wait, what?!” Liselotte was already nodding reflexively when she processed Rio’s answer in complete shock.

Rio chuckled at Liselotte’s surprise. “While I can’t do anything about how terrible the carriage itself looks, fortunately the wheels and axles haven’t been damaged irreparably. If I make some temporary repairs, it should be able to hold on until you reach Amande.”

Aria was pleased to see the rare sight of her master’s surprise and was smiling along softly. Chloe was also watching Liselotte’s expression as though she was witnessing a rare sight.

Liselotte noticed their gazes and cleared her throat in embarrassment. “...That is... most fortunate indeed.”

“Then I shall begin the repairs immediately. However, repairs of the metal roofing will be impossible to perform here, so may I ask for your permission to cut it off?”

“Cut it... off?” Rio’s question made Liselotte tilt her head curiously.

“The dent is blocking entry into the carriage and the weight of the steel may cause burden for the carriage itself. I believe it’d be better to lighten the weight, but if it is an issue I can figure something else out...”

“No, no, that won’t be a problem...” Liselotte said, confused. While she understood his intention, she couldn’t figure out how he could perform such a task.

“Then, please stand back,” Rio said, immediately beginning his work. Drawing the sword at his waist out of its sheath, he approached the overturned carriage.

“?!”

A flash. The steel roofing was cleanly sheared off from the body of the carriage, as though it had been sliced like paper. Liselotte and her attendants widened their eyes at the sight.

However, the steel plate was too large to cut down all at once, so Rio repeatedly changed locations and swung his sword with skill. Once the steel had been completely detached from the carriage, Liselotte somehow managed to voice her thoughts. “...Your skill is truly impressive.”

“It’s all thanks to this sword,” Rio answered, holding the dwarf-made sword out to show them.

“You were controlling the wind with that sword in the battle earlier... That’s an enchanted sword, right? And one of an ancient artifact class...” Liselotte asked hesitantly.

Enchanted swords were broadly defined as swords with sorcery embedded within them, but the precise definition referred to it being ancient sorcery — sorcery that couldn’t be reproduced using modern sorcery. Most people used the word in the narrower sense, but that didn’t mean the broader sense of the word wasn’t used.

The abilities of Rio’s sword allowed him to cross swords with a minotaur head-on and fire a finishing blow in the form of a wind blast on par with higher class magic. It clearly deviated from what could be made with modern sorcery in the Strahl region. Thus, Liselotte suspected Rio’s sword was an enchanted sword in the narrower meaning of the term.

However, enchanted swords of an ancient artifact class weren’t exactly an item in common circulation, and even if one was on the market, it wouldn’t be a price a commoner could afford. Even Liselotte only had a few to her name — one of which she had equipped on her confidant, Aria.

“A close friend bestowed it upon me. I have been using it carefully,” Rio revealed partially, nodding without hesitation. He wanted Liselotte to misunderstand the strength he had shown in the earlier fight and attribute it all to the sword. While Rio’s sword did have sorcery within it, its true effect was to take the user’s spirit arts and wrap it around the sword. Incidentally, that effect also increased the power of the spirit arts.

Rio had no intention of spreading the knowledge of spirit arts throughout Strahl, so it was more convenient for him to let others believe that he had been fighting with the abilities of the enchanted sword instead.

“Oh my, is that so...” Liselotte’s eyes widened.

At the very least, that means he’s someone who can be entrusted with that sword. What a mysterious person. But he’s personable, skilled, and he did save us. It would be rude to pry too deeply into him. I hope we can establish some kind of friendly relationship, though... she thought.

“All that’s left is to reattach the wheels and turn the carriage back up, then perform a final check for any other problems. It is not something you need trouble yourself with, Lady Liselotte, if you wish to return to directing others. They seem to be awaiting your orders over there.” Rio looked at the road behind them as he spoke to Liselotte. At the end of his gaze were several curious attendants watching them.

When Liselotte noticed the attendants gazing at them from afar, she sighed quietly. “...Then I shall take my leave. I will leave my attendant Aria here, so please inform her if you need any assistance. Let’s go, Chloe.”

“Y-Yes, ma’am!” Chloe responded in a fluster, following after Liselotte. Just before they left, she shot an interested look at Rio.

“I’m leaving the rest to you, Aria. If you need any more hands, don’t hesitate to ask.” Liselotte winked a discreet wink at Aria with those words before she left. It was most likely an order to analyze Rio while the two of them were alone.

Aria understood her master’s intent with just a look. She nodded respectfully. “...Leave it to me.”

◇　◇　◇

“What are you girls loafing around for?” Once Liselotte and Chloe returned to the main road, Liselotte sighed tiredly as she addressed the attendants gathered there. Cosette took a step forward on behalf of the rest.

“We were waiting for your next orders, Lady Liselotte. The knights said they’ll be watching our surroundings and gathering the enchanted gems, and we finished healing the wounded people and horses. We’ve also finished collecting the scattered belongings,” she replied with a grin.

“I see,” Liselotte replied, a sigh mixed into her voice. They had completed all the duties they were to do, she couldn’t really find fault with them. Then, a different attendant — Natalie — stepped forth.

“Also, regarding the disposal of the great sword stuck in the road, the knights said they would handle that after the collection of enchanted gems... As it seems we lack the hands to move it ourselves.” Natalie glanced at the corner of the road as she gave her additional report. There, the minotaur’s stone great sword was stabbed into the ground. It was roughly three meters in diameter.

“Right, we have to deal with that, too...” Liselotte recalled the earlier fight as she looked up the stone sword in a daze. In contrast, the attendant girls’ gazes were all drawn to the side forest where Rio was repairing the carriage.

“Umm, that really was an impressive fight earlier. Did you manage to find out anything about him?” Natalie asked hesitantly, looking at Rio. Even someone as serious as her couldn’t help but feel curious about him.

“That’s right! Who exactly is that ridiculously strong and handsome young man?” Cosette asked, brimming with curiosity. The other attendant girls also listened intently.

“...Apparently, Chloe’s acquaintance,” Liselotte said nonchalantly.

“Eh?!” Chloe hadn’t been expecting the sudden spotlight and flinched.

“Hey, that’s not fair, Chloe. Don’t hog him all to yourself. Introduce us later,” Cosette replied, immediately closing in on Chloe, who just shook her head in a fluster.

“N-No! By acquaintance, he just stayed at my family’s inn for a single night in the past, it’s not like we’re close enough for me to be introducing anyone!” Chloe shook her head in a fluster.

“Aww, really? I think that’s more than enough of an excuse to get close to him, though. Do you have any stories from back then? I want to hear more,” Cosette pressed, hounding Chloe for more details.

“That’s enough, Cosette. You’re bothering Chloe,” Natalie chided her with an exasperated look.

“Honestly, this is why you don’t have a single lover, you know?” Cosette sighed.

“Wha — I don’t want to hear that from you! It’s not a matter of the more the merrier, you know?!” Natalie complained with a red face.

“Okay, enough of that. No one wants to hear you two bicker all day again.” Liselotte put a stop to the two of them tiredly.

“Ahaha.” The other attendant girls laughed in amusement. Cosette and Natalie exchanged a look before pouting in slight embarrassment.

Meanwhile, Chloe’s attention was pulled toward Rio as he repaired the carriage in the woods. Her face seemed a little saddened, which made Liselotte notice her gloomy mood. “What’s wrong, Chloe?” she asked immediately.

“Ah, no, it’s nothing, my lady.” Chloe shook her head awkwardly.

“I know. You used to like him... am I right?” Cosette questioned with a teasing grin.

“Y-You’re wrong! That’s not what it is! And anyway, he doesn’t seem to remember me...” Chloe objected in a fluster, shoulders slumping dejectedly.

Her words seemed to trigger even greater curiosity within Cosette. “Hmm... It looks like you’ll have to tell us more about what happened.”

“Before that, you girls will distribute drinking water to the knights retrieving the enchanted gems. Then, do one more check for any more fragmented rubble scattered around the area,” Liselotte said, putting a stop to the chatter.

“Okay, Grace’s group will prepare the water for the knights! That means I’m free to assist Sir Haruto if needed!” Cosette replied energetically, looking in Rio’s direction as she offered her help.

Liselotte shook her head with a smile. “Absolutely not. You’ll only be in the way if you go. Now, get to work!”

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, Rio was repairing the carriage with very skilled hands. Since he didn’t need any help at the moment, Aria simply watched him work from the side.

“...You really are most proficient at this,” she said, the tone of her voice revealing her complete awe.

“I learned simple carpentry skills during my travels around various places,” Rio replied as he reattached a wheel to the body of the carriage.

“That’s wonderful. You also showed incredible sword skills in the fight earlier.”

“I’m just blessed with a brilliant weapon.”

“You jest. While it is true your enchanted sword is impressive in itself, what I witnessed of the sword user were skills above that. That amount of ability is not something that can be achieved so easily. You must have done some substantial training, no?” Aria asked.

“Thank you very much. I have made sure to keep up my training without fail ever since I was young. I saw that you have excellent skills yourself, Aria.”

“Thank you for the kind words. I was scouted by my lady for my sword skills. Oh, do excuse me... I must be distracting you from your work with this conversation,” Aria apologized with a strained smile.

Rio shook his head softly. “No, it makes for a nice change of pace. I do not mind continuing, if you are so inclined.” Just like how Aria and Liselotte were interested in Rio, Rio was also curious about Liselotte and Celia’s old friend, Aria. He wanted to talk to her while they were alone.

“Of course, it would be my pleasure,” Aria agreed readily.

“...Then, may I ask you something regarding what you said before?”

Aria nodded. “Sure.”

“Have you been working for Lady Liselotte for a while?”

“You could say that. I believe it’s been about five years since I officially started working for her.” Aria replied as she reflected on the past.

“Five years ago... That was before Amande went through its huge growth advancement, right?”

“Yes. It was shortly before my master took on her position as Amande’s governor, right as the Ricca Guild was being established. Although we actually became acquainted before that.”

Rio paused in his work for a moment and smiled pleasantly at her. “Then it sounds like you really are Lady Liselotte’s most trusted confidant.”

“I would like to think that,” Aria said, a somewhat uneasy smile on her face. “Speaking of which, Sir Haruto, you mentioned that you visited Amande several years ago. Perhaps we have passed by each other before,” she said with a smile.

“That’s possible. I only stayed for a single night, but when I visited again recently I was shocked to see how much the city had developed in only a few years.” Rio replied, resuming his work.

“It’s an honor to hear that. Ever since being appointed as governor, my master has been putting her all into the development of the city.”

“I’ve traveled through many places, but I do believe Amande is amazing. It has been such a pleasant place to visit, that I find myself stopping by more frequently as of late.”

“Oh, is that so? If my lady were to hear that, she would be most pleased.” Aria bowed happily to Rio.

“Then please, do inform her. I have especially been in the care of the Ricca Guild for all my shopping,” Rio said with a grin.

At that, Aria smiled. “I will make sure to let her know,” she replied in her melodic voice. “On that note, if I may ask purely out of my own curiosity... have you been traveling for a long time, Sir Haruto? From what I can see, you still seem to be in your mid to late teens.”

Rio thought for a brief moment before deciding to mix truth and falsehood in his answer. “...Yes, I’ve been traveling from the age of eleven. I am sixteen right now, so that would make my journey roughly five years long. I believe the first time I visited Amande was around four years ago.” Now that he had encountered Flora and the others unexpectedly, he added some fake points into his timeline, just in case.

“From such a young age... I also became an adventurer at a young age, but I was a few years older than that. Actually, at the age of eleven, you wouldn’t be able to register as an adventurer, would you?” Aria asked, eyes widening slightly. The Adventurer’s Guild had a general rule that one had to be at the age of twelve or above to register as an adventurer.

“Yes. Or rather, I still haven’t registered as an adventurer even now. It wasn’t something particularly necessary for me to travel around various kingdoms. That is why my main source of income was from liquidating the enchanted gems dropped by monsters I defeated along the way in the name of training,” Rio explained, revealing the fact he wasn’t an adventurer.

The adventurer guild was an international organization established by consignment of each kingdom. The original goal of the establishment was to force those unfit for working in regular society into the short-staffed national defense, putting them indirectly under the management of the kingdom and making them do labor effectively.

However, the international organization was in name only. While the organization headquarters formally did exist, its management was conducted by independent branches in each kingdom. The reason for this was each kingdom needed to dispatch their own official to supervise the branch operations, which made it impossible to cross national barriers.

Furthermore, becoming an adventurer required registration at either the branch office or main headquarters, each with their own advantages and disadvantages. For example, joining a branch office meant restrictions against working under other branches (in this regard, joining the headquarters meant ability to move freely between branches).

“...True, while joining a guild as an adventurer does grant benefits from the organization, it also means that your actions may also become restricted. I’ve heard of people who dislike that and choose not to become adventurers, too,” Aria said eloquently.

Who is he? What is he traveling for? The mysteries keep growing deeper with him, she thought at the same time.

“That should do it. I’m going to move the carriage back upright now, so please stand back a little.” Rio said, having reattached the wheel successfully.

“That must be difficult to do alone. Allow me to help,” Aria offered.

Rio shook his head. “No, the physical body enhancement of this sword is enough for me to manage alone.”

“All the more for me to help. I have also been entrusted with an enchanted sword from my master, so please leave it to me,” Aria said, refusing to back down. After being left here with the purpose of assisting, she didn’t feel it was right to leave everything to Rio.

“I’ll be fine, so please continue to be on guard of our surroundings,” Rio said, holding his right hand out and placating Aria from taking action.

“However...” Aria paused on her feet. The knights have already been doing that for a while now... she thought regretfully. She knew that Rio had to be more than aware that the knights were patrolling the area. That was why Aria thought he was probably offering her an excuse to take a break.

After that, Rio held his sword in his left hand and swung it in a show of drawing out the sword’s power — when he was actually using his own spirit arts to strengthen his body.

“Up we go.” Rio immediately dropped the sword and used both hands to grip the carriage firmly, lifting it easily.

Aria’s eyes widened faintly. “...Splendid,” she complimented. The attendants and knights nearby on the road were also taken aback, their gazes stolen by the sight of Rio lifting the carriage.

“All I did it was lift it up. It’s the enchanted sword’s doing.” Rio said to Aria, implying their reactions were over the top.

“No, maintaining the enhancement after releasing the sword requires advanced control of your magic essence. And yet, you are doing that so easily.”

When continuous sorcery like physical body enhancement was activated via magic artifact, it was generally quite difficult to maintain that sorcery after releasing the artifact. On top of that, the types of artifacts that required essence manipulation to activate the sorcery rather than a verbal spell chant tended to fluctuate erratically in performance. That characteristic was especially notable in ancient artifact class enchanted swords with high level sorcery embedded within. If the user’s control of magic essence was lacking, they wouldn’t be able to bring out the full potential of the artifact — in some cases failing to even activate the sorcery.

While Aria could perform the same stunt as Rio now, when she first received the enchanted sword from Liselotte, she had to go through rigorous training to be able to use it fully. At the very least, she couldn’t do it at Rio’s age. It was proof that Rio had that high of a control over his magic essence, or so Aria had judged.

“...Well, it has been two years since I started using this sword.” Rio said, gazing into the distant sky vacantly. While he had to adjust his story in order to hide the existence of spirit arts, in doing so he realized how much time had passed and felt nostalgic.

“...” The impression Aria received from peering at Rio’s profile was both mature and childish at the same time, making her eyes widen with curiosity.

“I’m going to check for any abnormalities with the wheels on the other side. If there are no other issues, it can be carried to the road,” Rio said, rounding to the other side of the carriage that had been facing the ground earlier. For a brief instant, he glanced at Aria’s face.

Aria, huh. It’s the same name that the Professor mumbled earlier, so she must be the same person. She doesn’t seem like a bad person either. ...But for some reason, both her name and face feel familiar somehow, he thought, feeling rather peculiar.

◇　◇　◇

In the end, the carriage was deemed to have escaped from any irreparable damage. Upon returning to the main road, Aria immediately reported to Liselotte, who was cleaning the area with the other attendant girls.

“My lady, the emergency repairs on the horse carriage have been completed.”

Liselotte’s expression brightened. “Really?! Wait, and you even brought it all the way here!” When she spotted Rio clutching a rope and towing the carriage behind him, she was slightly astonished.

“Sorry for the wait,” Rio said to Liselotte, pulling the carriage onto the road.

“...I do apologize, Sir Haruto, for making you transport the carriage after repairing it.” Liselotte bowed her head at Rio apologetically.

“No — Aria also helped push from behind for most of the way. I borrowed the power of my enchanted sword, too, so it was much easier to handle than the attack from the minotaur,” Rio joked, shaking his head.

“Why, how reliable you are,” Liselotte giggled. Cosette suddenly approached, politely offering Rio a wooden mug to drink from.

“Sir Haruto, please accept something to drink.” It was brimming with a sweet fruit juice inside.

“Oh, thank you very much for the offer. Erm...” Rio bowed, thanking her pleasantly but finding himself lacking knowledge of her name.

“Do forgive me. My name is Cosette. I’m an attendant serving Lady Liselotte.” Cosette pinched the hem of her attendant uniform and curtseyed in an elegant manner.

“Pff...” Liselotte and Aria, who were familiar with Cosette’s true form, were just barely able to hold back their laughter at the sight of her enthusiasm.

“Thank you very much, Miss Cosette,” Rio said cheerfully, having not noticed the expressions of the other two twitching with laughter.

“I would also like to thank you for what you did for us earlier. It may be impudent of me to speak out like this, but I wanted to convey my gratitude. Please forgive my rudeness,” Cosette said, lowering her head deep in a show of respect.

Rio tilted his head with a troubled look. “It was nothing. And I am not a noble, so you do not need to act so formally with me.”

“I cannot accept that. My master owes Sir Haruto her life. Now, I shall take my leave from here... Thank you for your time.” Cosette shook her head gracefully and bowed her head before turning. With that clear message conveyed, she turned and left with the grace of a swan.

“Seeing Cosette and Aria, it seems all your attendants are very well-trained, Lady Liselotte,” Rio said in awe.

“No, well... Thank you.” Liselotte nodded her head with a frown.

◇　◇　◇

Shortly after that, the knights that were on patrol for enchanted gems and possible threats started to return one by one. Once the knights were rehydrated, Duke Huguenot came over as well; they decided they would attempt to move the minotaur sword that was obstructing passage through the road.

“Now, let us move this to the side of the road.”

“I was the one who threw it at the ground. If you would like, I could be retrieve it myself...” Rio suggested.

“Hmm... Wouldn’t that be a little too difficult for you to do alone? I believe catching it in the air and swinging it is a much different burden to lifting it off the ground...” Duke Huguenot stated logically.

“Allow me to make an attempt first, then,” Rio said, squeezing the handle of his still sheathed sword and making a show of swinging it as though to draw out the enchanted power. He walked closer to the great sword, grabbing the stone sword that was several times taller than him.

“...Hah!” With a small breath, he exerted his strength. The great sword that was pierced into the ground creaked as it started to lift up. After a moment, it was pulled completely free.

“Oooh!” Cheers rose around Rio.

“It’s dangerous, so please stand back.” Unfortunately, the blade was rather long, so Rio warned the knights and attendant girls nearby to be careful.

Liselotte watched Rio with wide eyes. “...Could you do the same thing?” she asked Aria, who stood beside her.

“I won’t know until I try it for myself, but... I believe it should be possible,” Aria replied quietly.

“Oi oi, it sure is rowdy out here.” Hiroaki appeared from the carriage. Apparently all the noise had caught his attention.

Flora spotted Rio holding the stone great sword and widened her eyes as she mumbled in awe. “...It seems Sir Haruto is carrying that sword.”

Meanwhile, Hiroaki’s eyes landed on the same scene. He stared at Rio gathering the attention with a rather indifferent look in his eyes. “Hah, I see...”

Still carrying the great sword, Rio slowly walked over to the forest at the side of the road. The knights and attendants murmured to themselves as they watched him do so.

Oh, great... Now they’re all in an uproar. Sure must be nice, being attractive. It’s like living life in easy mode, having people fawn over you just for carrying something heavy... Hiroaki thought with an unamused face as he looked at the attendant girls fussing nearby. Even Liselotte was watching Rio with a look of awe on her face. Hiroaki found that fact the most unpleasant of all. In that time, Rio made it to the forest with the stone sword in hand and gently laid it down on its side in the forest.

Hiroaki sighed exasperatedly. I guess it’s time to show them the power of a true hero. He set off, walking towards Rio casually.

When Liselotte noticed that Hiroaki had alighted from the carriage, she called out to him. “...Hero?”

“Just watch this,” Hiroaki said with a smug look, heading towards the side of the road where Rio was. Rio had just stood up after his work was done and was turning on his heel to head back. He noticed Hiroaki approaching and tilted his head.

“Oh. Hello, hero. Is something the matter?”

“I was just wondering how heavy that stone sword was. Just lend it to me for a sec.” Hiroaki smirked with a huff, grabbing the sword Rio had laid on the floor with both hands. With an audible grunt, he attempted to lift it up. Then, though he swayed uneasily for a moment, Hiroaki managed to hold the stone great sword up perfectly.

“Ooh!” The knights raised their voices in a cheer.

Roanna immediately got close, too. “Why, that’s splendid, Sir Hiroaki.”

“Ah, it’s a little hard to carry because of its size, but I guess this should do it. It’s no big deal.” Hiroaki smiled smugly, full of confidence in himself.

The way he holds his body is completely amateur, but his enhanced abilities show promise. If he has this much strength, then he’s probably stronger than the average knight, so it makes sense that he would be confident in his strength. But... is this spirit arts? Rio analyzed to himself, eyes widening.

“That is very impressive, hero,” he praised Hiroaki as he pondered.

“Hahaha. Well, you’re not so bad yourself. Let’s go back.” Hiroaki lowered the stone great sword back to where it was and patted Rio on the shoulder before heading back to the carriage at a brisk walk. Roanna accompanied him. Her chest was puffed up proudly at all the attention gathered on Hiroaki. Rio’s lips upturned in a smile as he followed the two of them from behind.

Hiroaki made a beeline for Liselotte and called out to her, obviously in a good mood. “C’mon Liselotte, let’s go. Get in the carriage. You too, Flora.” He included Flora as an immediate afterthought.

“Ah, yes.” Flora replied first. Liselotte nodded respectfully, glancing at Rio.

“Understood. Then, may Sir Haruto accompany us? We’ll be heading towards Amande next...”

“I also have business in Amande, so I have no reason to object... But are you sure you want to let me in the carriage with you?” Rio asked, watching their party’s expression observantly. His social standing wasn’t appropriate to be riding with a hero, princess, duke, and two noble ladies. Normally, he wouldn’t even be permitted to ride with regular nobles.

“There’s no need to feel any kind of reservation. You did save all of our lives earlier, after all,” Duke Huguenot said, smiling merrily.

“That’s right, Sir Haruto. We also wanted to give our formal thanks, so please, you are more than welcome to join us,” Liselotte said, bowing her head deeply.

Rio tried to stop Liselotte in a fluster. “No, no, please raise your head, Lady Liselotte.”

“Yeah, he’s right. Someone as great as you shouldn’t be bowing your head so easily,” Hiroaki agreed.

“...Do excuse me for my behavior, then.” Liselotte said with a frown, looking at Rio.

“Now, let’s get going already. Come on,” Hiroaki said, heading towards the carriage first.

Thus, Rio followed Liselotte and the others to Amande.

◇　◇　◇

Liselotte led Rio to the carriage; he hesitantly stepped inside.

“...Excuse me.” The interior of the carriage was spacious and could fit eight people when seated together. There, Hiroaki, Flora, Roanna and Duke Huguenot took their seats first.

Hiroaki looked at Rio entering late. “Well, have a seat,” he said with a pompous air.

“Sir Haruto, please sit on this side,” Liselotte motioned to the highest remaining seat.

“Thank you for the hospitality.” Rio bowed politely before sitting down. Liselotte chose one seat down from Rio’s before sitting down too. It was the furthest from Hiroaki, who was seated in the highest position.

Hiroaki looked a little displeased at being further away from Liselotte, but he crossed his legs calmly. “So who are you, really? A noble from somewhere?” he asked Rio.

At that, Flora flinched. “Sir Hiroaki, asking such questions like that out of the blue... It’s rude to Sir Haruto,” she said to Hiroaki nervously, looking at Rio.

“Oi oi, are you telling me we didn’t let him onto the carriage just to ask that? We should just cut to the chase for this kind of thing.” Hiroaki gave an exaggerated shrug of his shoulders.

“H-However...” Flora watched Rio’s expression worriedly as she stumbled over her words. There was a proper manner and procedure for which such things should be done, so when those of higher status ignored the rules, it made it harder for others to speak up. That was how a society built on status operated, after all.

With a faint smile, Rio shook his head to show he wasn’t bothered. “Please, there is no need to concern yourselves over me. It is true my background hasn’t been made clear to you.”

“Well, from the looks of things, you’re just a swordsman traveling around while training your sword skills. A typical cliche setting, but that’s what makes it all the more suspicious. The guys outside were hasty to make a fuss about you, but I’d like to learn a bit more about your background before I trust you completely,” Hiroaki stated bluntly, addressing Rio. Meanwhile, Liselotte found herself fighting the urge to ignore their status difference and interrupt several times.

...He’s basically declaring his distrust towards him. Isn’t that a bit too rude towards the one who saved you? Even if you want to ask more, there should be a way to go about asking politely. His manners are all over the place.

But she had no choice but to stay silent; it would probably be best to thank him for the earlier fight at a later time without Hiroaki around, anyway. With that thought, Liselotte kept up the smile on her face.

“Naturally, I don’t expect everyone to believe me so easily either... But unfortunately, I do not possess anything that can objectively prove my identity,” Rio said with a frown.

“Well, the level of civilization in this world is what it is... If only you had something with a noble house crest on it, then you could prove yourself...” Hiroaki said, asking in a roundabout way whether he was a noble or not.

“As I said in the beginning, I am not a noble. If anything, I am a mere wanderer, a nomad that travels without a particular kingdom to call home,” Rio said as truthfully as he could.

“Hmm... So that’s why you’re traveling everywhere?” Hiroaki asked, looking at Rio doubtfully.

“Yes.” Rio nodded curtly.

“But doesn’t your speech and behavior seems to be rather educated for a wanderer?” Hiroaki asked, looking at Roanna. He had heard from her earlier about how Rio’s mannerisms didn’t seem like that of a regular commoner.

“...I’m honored that you think so. But it is merely a life skill I picked up along the way. Because I am a wanderer, I have to endeavor to live peacefully with people no matter where I go,” Rio said with a respectful bow.

“Hahaha. Well, you do seem to be able to speak well. I don’t know how nomads and refugees are treated in this world, to be honest, but... Actually, how are they treated, really?” Hiroaki asked those around him with a cheerful grin.

“...It’s not that they’re a target of aggressive discrimination, it’s just that they may be treated as inferior to locals that live in the area. That’s why there are many people who do not feel any attachment for the land and end up wandering from place to place,” Duke Huguenot, the eldest present and most well-versed with the world, answered.

“Ah, I see. So that’s how it is. Well, I get it... That’s a problem that exists in my world too. Sure causes lots of headaches. There may be talented people among refugees, but they can’t be treated with favoritism over the actual citizens of the nation. The more they stand out, the more the inferior locals will envy them, too,” Hiroaki said in comprehension.

“You are most knowledgeable, Sir Hiroaki,” Roanna said with a breath of awe.

“Eh, it’s no big deal. But I guess that does give some credit to your story about traveling around the world, more or less.” Hiroaki smirked smugly and looked at Rio.

“...I appreciate your kindness.” Rio forced a smile on his face and bowed his head politely.

“Well, you don’t seem like a bad guy. I suppose you can pass. At the very least, you now have a hero’s stamp of approval of being trustworthy.” Hiroaki laughed heartily as he spoke.

“That is an honor indeed.” Once more, Rio bowed his head in a polite manner.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, outside the carriage where Rio was riding with the others...

“Say, Aria. You spoke with Sir Haruto a little, right? What was he like?” Cosette asked Aria enthusiastically. At that, Natalie and Chloe, who had been walking nearby, also closed in on Cosette and Aria to eavesdrop on their conversation.

Aria felt the curiosity of her subordinates as clear as day. “...It seems he is one year older than our lady, but he seems very calm and mature for his age. He mentioned that he has been traveling for years now,” she replied with a sigh.

Cosette and Natalie were both veteran attendants too. Aria was their leader as the head of the attendants, but their long years of working together made them more akin to equal colleagues.

“Anything else? Like his ideal woman or something,” Cosette asked further, expression brimming with interest.

“There’s no way I could ask something so intrusive in such a short conversation,” Aria said with a tired look.

“But that’s like, something you can observe when you’re close up to him, no? Does he look like the type who likes quiet and graceful girls, or bright and talkative girls?” Cosette continued with a teasing wink.

“Unfortunately, I do not possess such observational skills.” Aria shook her head curtly.

“Oh my, I’m not sure I believe that,” Cosette objected. “For example, doesn’t the hero seem like he would prefer girls that are meek and obedient? Of course, they have to be extremely attractive first, but still.”

“H-Hey! That’s disrespectful... What would you do if someone overheard that?!” Natalie interrupted in a panic.

“Oh, were you listening? Eavesdropping isn’t very nice of you,” Cosette responded bluntly.

Chapter 2: Arrival in Amande

Rio, Liselotte’s party, and the others arrived in Amande. The carriage entered the city from the west gate and headed down the main street towards the city center, making its way to the northern district where Liselotte’s estate was located.

“Thank you for accompanying me this far, Lady Liselotte.” Rio was dropped off at the square in the center of the city to make his way to the accommodation that was prepared for him.

“It wasn’t a problem at all. I’ll send a messenger tomorrow morning, so please enjoy yourself for the rest of today. Aria, make sure you take care of Sir Haruto,” Liselotte said from where she was seeing Rio off outside the carriage.

“Understood,” Aria replied, nodding her head respectfully. Liselotte boarded the carriage once more and headed for her estate and Aria began her task of leading Rio.

“Allow me to show you the way, Sir Haruto. Please, follow me.”

“Of course.” Rio started walking after Aria. A moment later, they arrived at the inn.

“It’s over here.” The inn was located right in the square where the carriage had dropped them off. Being in the square at the center of the city, it was relatively close to Liselotte’s estate and was a highly desirable location.

“Why, this is a most spectacular inn.” Rio looked up at the inn he was led to with wide eyes. The three-storey building was made of elegant stone and seemed to be newly constructed, as it still appeared as such. There was no mistaking that it was of a higher class compared to the other luxury inns in the area.

“Thank you for the compliment. Please, come inside.” Aria bowed her head respectfully and approached the entrance of the building. Several employees were waiting on standby before the inn — They seemed to recognize Aria’s face, as they welcomed the two of them in without interruption.

“Please have a seat over here and wait a moment, Sir Haruto.” Aria had Rio seat himself on a sofa in the lobby before heading to the front desk alone. Then, a female employee wearing a waitress outfit approached him.

“Here you are, Sir Haruto,” The female employee said, placing a cup of tea down before the sofa. She must have heard his name from Aria. Then, not even a minute later, Aria returned.

“Sir Haruto, preparations of your room have been completed. I shall lead you to it now, so please, follow me.”

“Lead the way.” Rio stood up and bowed briefly before beginning to move. He was led to a room on the top floor of the building.

“Would this room suit your liking? It has multiple bedrooms, so your company may stay in separate rooms from you if they so wish,” Aria explained once they arrived.

Rio looked around the spacious room in awe. “Naturally, I would never find a fault with a room as wonderful as this...”

The space allocated to the living room easily surpassed fifteen square meters, and there were multiple bedrooms on top of that. It was a pinch smaller than the stone house Rio owned, but it was undoubtedly the suite room.

“If you are satisfied with this space, then you are free to stay here as long as you wish. It has been reserved for your use without limit. And there will be no need to worry about fees.” Aria bowed and spoke reverently. It was all rather lavish.

“...I am much obliged.” Rio said apologetically, accepting Liselotte’s goodwill.

◇　◇　◇

After Aria left the room, Rio sat down on the living room sofa and called out to Aishia through their telepathic connection. Aishia, can you hear me? For contract spirits like Aishia, it was possible to communicate with each other within a half kilometer radius.

Yup, I hear you, Aishia responded immediately, making Rio smile.

Thank goodness. Where are you right now? Since everything had happened so quickly, they had barely been able to communicate before parting, so Rio had feared he may have caused the two to worry.

Having tea with Celia at a nearby café.

Ahaha, I’m glad to hear that. They seemed to be having a more relaxing time than he expected, filling him with a sense of relief. However, that didn’t seem to be the case.

Celia’s worried, so come here quickly.

...Got it. There are things I want to tell you two, so I’ll be right there. Rio quietly stood up from the sofa.

◇　◇　◇

Rio left the key to his room with the front desk and headed outside to meet up with Aishia and Celia.

Just keep going straight like that. We’re in a cafe named Ciel — we’re on the balcony on the second floor. Following Aishia’s directions, Rio arrived at the aforementioned cafe.

“Welcome!” A pretty worker girl stood out front, welcoming Rio energetically.

“My companions have arrived already. May I head inside?”

“Of course. Go right ahead!” The girl agreed readily, leaving Rio to head up the staircase and towards the balcony. The balcony itself wasn’t very wide, having only enough room for one round table. Rio spotted Celia and Aishia sitting there right away.

“He’s here,” Aishia said, immediately noticing Rio’s arrival.

“Haruto!” Celia jumped up, running towards Rio worriedly.

“Umm. Sorry for the wait, Cecilia.” Rio smiled awkwardly, addressing Celia by her alias.

“Was everything okay? Are you hurt anywhere?” Celia asked worriedly, feeling all over Rio’s body with searching hands. The two of them were standing at the entrance to the balcony, in plain view of the customers inside.

“What’s this? The girl who was on the balcony is clinging to a man!”

“Isn’t he handsome?”

“The two that were sitting on the balcony seats were really cute, too.”

And so on. The female customers having tea at the cafe gossiped, their attention on the three.

“Ahaha, I’m not hurt at all, so please, don’t worry. It feels like everyone’s staring at us, so why don’t we sit down first?” Rio felt the gazes stabbing into his back from inside the store and suggested they sit down with a grimace.

“Y-Yeah.” Celia became aware of the fact that she was clinging to Rio and blushed furiously. She turned on her heel and timidly returned to her seat.

“Waitress, please bring me the cafe’s recommended tea.” Rio called out his order to the worker girl who had just come up the stairs to take his order, requesting an order of tea before going out on the balcony to sit next to Celia and Aishia.

“I apologize for making you worry, but the battle ended without incident. Cecilia’s friend was also completely unharmed, so you need not worry about her either,” he said to Celia. From this seat, the customers inside the cafe shouldn’t have been able to hear him. They would continue using aliases just in case, but their conversation should be fine to hold as long as they kept an eye out for the waitress. Incidentally, the table they were seated at already had several scones that they must have ordered earlier. Celia didn’t seem to have much of an appetite, but Aishia was still chewing away eagerly, even now.

“Y-Yeah. We were watching from above up until just before the battle ended...” Celia nodded hesitantly.

“Then you should know that I am not injured, no?” Rio chuckled in amusement.

“W-Watching you was nerve-racking! You may have been overwhelmingly strong, but the monsters you were facing were huge too!” Celia said, pouting her lips. Rio may have been overwhelming, but the sight of him crossing swords from head-on with such gigantic monsters was heartstopping. It was enough to make her worry that Rio was being hurt somewhere she couldn’t see with her naked eye.

“Ahaha. Maybe if I was still a kid, but I’m strong enough to go against those monsters head-to-head now.” Rio laughed blankly, shaking his head as though it was nothing at all.

“Head-to-head... Those were minotaurs. The absolute strongest of the monsters that haven’t been seen since the Divine War,” Celia said in half exasperation, face twitching.

“But even you would have been able to defeat them, given the right conditions. No?” Rio asked, giving Celia a piercing look. She had to have acquired several magics that could take down a minotaur in a single blow herself. She wasn’t called a genius sorceress for nothing.

“They move too fast, so I’d have to restrain them first, but... Wait, this isn’t about that! Why does it feel like you’re trying to divert the topic?!” Celia started seriously considering how she would have defeated them, but soon snapped back to her senses, as she was busy worrying about Rio right now. She didn’t want him in dangerous situations, after all.

“Ahaha, well, it looks like the tea is here, so let me explain what’s going to happen from now on,” Rio said with a faint smile, moving their talk forward.

“...Okay,” Celia pouted, but nodded obediently.

“Excuse me. Here is the black tea you ordered.” The worker girl stepped out onto the balcony and carefully set down a tea set before retreating immediately. Once Rio had confirmed she was gone, he began speaking.

“First, we’ll be staying within the city of Amande for the next few days. Our accommodations have been prepared by Cecilia’s friend, Aria, so we’ll be staying there for the duration of the trip. I’m sorry to be springing this upon you without notice... I hope that’s okay?”

Aishia paused mid-mouthful of a scone and gave an immediate response that showed she didn’t particularly care. “It’s fine.”

Despite her agreement, Celia’s face darkened with worry. “Of course, I don’t mind either... but I’ll have to be careful not to meet Aria. Well, I doubt she’d recognize me if we just passed by each other on the streets...”

“You give off quite a different impression to what you used to be like, so I think it’ll be fine. But Aria won’t be the only person you need to be aware of...” Rio said carefully, reluctant to speak up.

“...Is something wrong?” Celia tilted her head curiously.

Rio found his resolution and nervously revealed the truth. “Umm, there are actually visitors of Beltrum’s royalty and nobility here at the moment.”

“Eh?!” Celia’s eyes widened in shock.

“Yeah, I was surprised too. I didn’t notice until the battle was over.” During the battle, Flora had been hiding out of sight, and Aria’s fighting drew the majority of the attention. That’s why Celia and even Rio hadn’t noticed.

“W-Who was there?” Celia asked nervously.

“It turned out that other than Liselotte and her attendants, everyone else there was from the kingdom of Beltrum. The estranged faction of Duke Huguenot, to be precise. Second Princess Flora, Duke Huguenot, as well as Roanna from Duke Fontaine’s faction, are also here,” Rio said, listing off the most important figures.

“...They’re all major figures.” And they were all people that Celia knew of. “Wait, Roanna was your classmate and Princess Flora should have known you well too. Didn’t they realize?” Celia noticed in a panic.

“Yes. Princess Flora has a good intuition and seemed to sense something was odd, but Roanna didn’t seem to notice anything in particular,” Rio replied readily.

“...Hey, wouldn’t it be better if we left Amande immediately?” Celia suggested with a slightly panicked look. “No, we will stay in Amande.” Rio shook his head in blunt refusal, his decision firm.

“Someone might find out, though.”

“The greatest danger is Princess Flora, but we haven’t seen each other in years. Not to mention the fact that my hair color is different now. I believe the risk is within a reasonable limit.”

Outside of using dyes, there was no way of changing hair color in the Strahl region, but the concept of dyeing hair wasn’t a common idea among the general public to begin with. Even if one did dye their hair, it would look far more unnatural compared to Rio’s use of magic artifacts.

“...Is there a reason?”

“Yes. I wish to establish favorable relations with Liselotte. She is the daughter of the Galarc Kingdom’s great lord, Duke Cretia, and the president of the Ricca Merchant Guild.”

“With Liselotte?” Celia’s eyes widened at the unexpected response.

“Yes. I figured it wouldn’t hurt to have a connection to someone powerful within this kingdom, in case the hero I am searching for is affiliated with the Galarc Kingdom and I needed a way to meet them formally. That’s why I want to earn her favor. Of course, saving your friend was also one of my goals, but the main reason why I intervened in the earlier battle was because of this,” Rio revealed honestly. On top of those reasons, forming a favorable relationship with Liselotte might also prove useful one day if they were ever to return Celia to the world of nobility, Rio thought.

“...Okay. Yeah, I understand.” Celia hesitated for a long minute, but seemed to reach an understanding as she nodded soon after.

“I’m glad to hear it. I was actually expecting more opposition than that,” Rio said a little unexpectedly.

“...It’s not like you’re trying to do something dangerous, right?” Celia asked, watching Rio’s face carefully.

“Of course not,” Rio affirmed immediately.

“Then I’ll believe in you. That’s been my decision from the get-go.” Celia smiled gently as she spoke.

“Cecilia...” Rio felt strangely embarrassed, but at the same time, happiness surged within him.

“But you mustn’t let your guard down, understood? She may seem like a girl close to your age, but Liselotte is well known for being a more than capable bigshot noble,” Celia warned. She was still Rio’s professor in areas like this.

“Yes.” Rio nodded his head happily.

“What are you so happy for? Well, whatever. I’m happy to answer any questions you might have, so feel free to ask me more, okay?” Celia offered shyly.

“Thank you very much. Actually, I had plans to meet Liselotte once again tomorrow. Could you teach me some of the etiquette involved in visiting the estate of a noble?” Rio smiled softly, immediately taking Celia up on her offer. She nodded happily.

“Yup, leave it to me!” Celia nodded happily.

◇　◇　◇

After that, Rio, Celia, and Aishia chatted at the cafe for a while before heading to the inn. Aishia seemed to have acquired a taste for scones ever since the one she ate in Cleia and was more satisfied than usual.

“By the way, what kind of person is Liselotte?” Celia asked Rio on the way.

“She has a soft demeanor, but is a very intelligent woman. I suppose it makes sense that your friend would want to serve her.” Rio looked up at the skies as he thought back on his first impression of Liselotte.

“I see.” Celia smiled somewhat shyly. She must have been proud to hear her friend being praised.

“Speaking of which, is your friend — Aria — also from the kingdom of Beltrum?” Rio asked.

“Yup. She used to be my classmate at the Royal Academy of Beltrum, but, well... her house fell into ruin. She ended up dropping out of the academy. But she was an outstanding person, so she found employment at the castle easily. Though, the harassment got too much for her to bear, so she quit pretty shortly after that,” Celia explained.

Rio recalled the way Aria fought in the earlier battle and spoke in awe. “True, she did have a splendid sword arm from what I witnessed.”

“Yeah, back at the academy her marks in swordcraft could hold down the boys. She always came out on top.” Celia boasted proudly.

“I see. As a young and skilled female knight, it must have been hard for her to deal with the biased views of those around her.” Rio imagined the circumstances of Aria at the time with a bitter smile. The harassment was strong against Rio, who was an orphan on the streets, so it must have been tough on a fallen noble.

“Eh?” Celia made a confused face.

“...Umm, did I say something strange? She was a knight, wasn’t she?” Rio also cocked his head curiously.

“Ohh, no no, that wasn’t it. Ah, I see... it would’ve been more natural for her to have been a knight, huh? Anyway, she was actually working as the head servant of the castle.” Celia giggled as she corrected Rio’s misunderstanding. The head servant was in charge of welcoming guests and ensuring they were comfortable; one had to be of the proper origins in order to do so.

“I see... I jumped to conclusions. Forgive me,” Rio apologized with a faint smile.

“Wait... hmm. Come to think of it, you should’ve met Aria once before too,” Celia suddenly said.

“R-Really?” Rio was taken aback, questions on his tongue.

“Yup. When you were seven years old and had been first summoned to the royal castle. Do you remember the girl who was in charge of looking after you, just before your audience with His Majesty?”

Rio finally remembered. “...Aah, the girl from back then. I had no idea at all.” His eyes widened to round circles as he recalled the fateful encounter.

“Fufu, I don’t blame you for forgetting. It’s been nine years, after all.” Celia smiled in amusement.

“Right,” Rio agreed with a huff.

“She actually quit her castle duties shortly after that. Then, she picked up the sword and became an adventurer, which is where Liselotte scouted her. I’ve met her several times since then, but it seems like she’s having the time of her life now.” Celia said, looking into the distance with a smile.

◇　◇　◇

At the Amande governor’s estate, Liselotte was seeing to a one-on-one meeting with Duke Huguenot after allocating a guest room for Hiroaki, Flora, and Roanna.

“My goodness, have things taken a turn for the terrible ever since that dragon-like creature appeared.” Duke Huguenot lowered himself onto the sofa and began to speak with tired finality.

“My apologies. I have caused you a fair amount of trouble... There were even people from your side who were injured.” Liselotte frowned apologetically.

“No, we were the ones who insisted on accompanying you. Just because we were met with an unexpected enemy attack does not mean you bear the responsibility. There were serious injuries, but at least no one was killed. As long as we fulfilled our role as guards, then all is well.” Duke Huguenot shook his head warmly.

“...I am most grateful for that. It was most fortunate that the knights had a very sturdy defense. If I were traveling alone with only my followers, I do not believe we would have made it out without any deaths,” Liselotte replied respectfully.

“No no, I heard your attendant ladies played quite an impressive part of the battle, too. Especially Aria. Raymond, the leader of the elite guards, was insisting that her strength could even reach that of the King’s Sword.”

“Why, did he really? I’ll be sure to pass that on to her later, then.” Liselotte smiled happily.

“...It appears our kingdom really did release a wonderful talent, regretful as it may be. But I am in awe of your abilities in having selected someone of her worth.” Duke Huguenot chuckled, shrugging his shoulders with exasperation.

“But Aria alone would not have been able to overcome that crisis. Minotaurs and unknown humanoid monsters... The battlefield immediately took a turn for the worse when they appeared.” Liselotte recalled the events with a dark grimace.

“Hmm. Of the four minotaurs that appeared, your Aria defeated one, right? I heard the humanoid monsters that spawned at the same time were fairly powerful opponents too. It was most commendable how she was able to escape unaided after being surrounded. But the boy who appeared after that left an extreme impression too. His power was truly overwhelming. If he hadn’t appeared, we may have been wiped out.” Duke Huguenot analyzed the events of the attack calmly.

“...However, wouldn’t the hero have the power to overturn that situation, if it came down to it?”

“Hahaha, perhaps. But the hero lacks real experience in battles — even you should be aware of that, I am sure.” Duke Huguenot laughed inappropriately, questioning her in return.

“...I suspected as much, but to be honest, I still have not been able to adequately measure how much power the hero has within him. He does not appear to have any substantial practical training, but he was able to pick up the minotaur’s sword. Was he only able to accomplish that because he brought out the power of the Divine Arms?” Liselotte asked, speaking honestly of her impressions of Hiroaki.

“Yes, you can consider Divine Arms to be in the same category as enchanted swords. It’s similar to how compatibility with the weapon brings out more power, but in the case of Divine Arms that compatibility is limited to the hero alone. Although there are irregular cases where the power of a Divine Arms can be drawn freely or without any training. There are many mysteries surrounding the topic, but heroes and Divine Arms are certainly special,” Duke Huguenot said, nodding his head deeply.

“Which means what your hero is lacking is real battle experience after all?” Liselotte asked with a serious expression.

“Indeed, he does. Well, it appears he never had any combat training to begin with, and we do not wish for our precious hero to be placed in danger either. Thinking it premature for him to experience real battle, we had limited his training to casual mock battles with the knights. Recently, he’s building his confidence through consecutive wins, so we were considering moving him onto low level monsters and experience the air of a real battle, but...”

It appeared as though the air of a real battle was different. Regardless of the fact Hiroaki held such a mighty power as a hero, when he felt his life was in danger, he became nervous — and useless.

“His first battle turned out to be a rather heavy experience.” Liselotte let a bitter smile show.

“That it did, that it did. But real battles never go according to plan anyway. At least it became a valuable experience, if we were to think of it optimistically,” Duke Huguenot said with a hint of a bitter smile.

Based on their conversation until now, Liselotte formed her guess of Duke Huguenot’s thoughts. So it seems that Duke Huguenot really isn’t using him for anything other than a symbol of divine will, for now. His use in battle comes secondary, which is exactly what I expected.

Similarly, Liselotte agreed with Duke Huguenot’s perception of political balance. It would be a different case if a large scale war was on the horizon, but at present there was no need for the hero to flaunt his power and leave a legend. At worst, it could be perceived as a threat to the neighboring kingdoms, after all.

And, unlikely as it may be, if the hero became so absorbed with his own power he separated from the kingdom, that power would be pointed towards them instead. Because of that, this was the time to be ascertaining the hero’s personality and building trust in their relationship.

“By the way, on a slightly different note, could we discuss the boy a little?” Duke Huguenot’s tone changed as he spoke solemnly.

“...You mean Sir Haruto, yes?”

“He defeated three of the four minotaurs that appeared. He also eliminated several of the mysterious but powerful humanoid monsters... An impossible feat had he not had full control over his enchanted sword. Honestly speaking, what do you think of that extremely powerful enchanted swordsman, Liselotte?”

“...Based on his speech and conduct — and of course, his sword mastery — I felt a sense of elegance and refinement. While I can understand why someone of nomad origins would need such behavior...”

“There are still many unexplained points there. Although, the possibility of him being a secret agent shouldn’t be dismissed either, I find it more likely that he is a noble in hiding due to some circumstance or another, or perhaps someone from a fallen noble family?”

“...Yes, there are cases like Aria’s, too. If he was from a fallen noble family, I can understand why he wouldn’t want to speak of his own background. As for the other possibility, I have nothing to offer there,” Liselotte agreed, speaking eloquently.

“I figured. As we continue building our relationship with him, I would like to learn more about his background...”

“However, it would be a bad move to show any signs of our suspicions. It would be most improper to be discourteous to the one who saved us, and for someone of his skill, I wish to treat him carefully and build a relationship of trust.”

If they interacted while using a heavy-handed approach, it could result in antagonizing themselves foolishly.

“I feel the same. It seems we really are on the same page,” Duke Huguenot said with a chuckle.

“What do you mean?” The normally sharp Liselotte seemed to feign ignorance.

“Hahaha, how harsh of you. I mean in our desire to build trust with him. With our eyes set on the same person, it would be best to have our first step planned in advance. Wouldn’t you agree?” Duke Huguenot laughed heartily, coaxing Liselotte to respond.

“Do you wish to sit in on our meeting tomorrow?” Liselotte asked with a small sigh.

“I’m glad you’re quick on the uptake. I wish to meet him more for the sake of the future, too.” Duke Huguenot nodded firmly.

“I understand. Then I shall set up such a meeting for you,” Liselotte agreed easily.

At any rate, the hero will probably demand to sit in as well. If I have to do this either way, at least giving permission beforehand counts as doing a small favor, she thought.

“As a token of my gratitude, feel free to use my knights as you wish. Naturally, you will be conducting investigations into the mass spawning of monsters, no? If you are to search the forests, the more hands on deck, the better,” Duke Huguenot suggested as compensation.

Liselotte gave a radiant smile. “Why, that would be a great help. I was thinking of sending only the best people.”

“Abnormal situations have been occurring continuously, including the appearance of that dragon-like creature. I’m sure it has been a source of many headaches, what with all the incidents being caused by matters not of mankind.”

“...Yes. Actually, there were reports of adventurers going missing some time ago, which could possibly be related to the mass spawns of monsters.” Liselotte frowned bitterly.

“I understand how you must feel,” Duke Huguenot murmured, sighing quietly.

“I have no words for all the trouble we must have caused you, having you come here at such troubling times.”

“Hahaha. No no, we were the ones who chose to visit you unannounced. I should be the one apologizing for visiting uninvited at such a busy time.”

“That is no trouble at all, but... Did you come here with some business in mind, Duke Huguenot?”

“Oh yes, now that you mention it... all the events up until now have completely distracted me from our original goal.” Duke Huguenot shrugged with a faint smile.

“Which is...?” Liselotte cocked her head, inquiring after his intentions.

“It’s about Charles Arbor’s wedding ceremony. We received information that due to certain circumstances, the bride Celia was abducted. I wanted to hear your story, as someone who was present.”

“...Is that so? Information travels fast.” Liselotte said, impressed. I had assumed the mastermind behind the incident was Duke Huguenot, but could I be wrong? Contrary to her outward attitude, she analyzed his words calmly.

“I would like you to tell me more about it. To be honest, I am not sure which force would be behind it.”

“I’d be happy to.”

Thus, the two began their discussion about Celia’s abduction.

Chapter 3: Intruders

Back in the Kingdom of Galarc, in the city of Amande, the night after Rio had defeated the minotaurs and saved the day...

The cafeteria on the first floor of the Ricca Guild inn that Rio was staying at was also open to the general public as a luxury high end restaurant. Rio was enjoying dinner with Celia and Aishia in a private room; directly opposite to the door of the private room they were using was an open window. It allowed them to look over the spacious back courtyard as they enjoyed the finest food and liquor, and on days with good weather, the terrace was open for seating, too.

“Having such a wide garden at the back of an inn is wonderful. It’s been well maintained.” Celia gazed at the garden in an uplifted mood as she waited for the next dish to be carried out.

“It’s an inn. Would be perfect if it had a bathtub deep enough to submerge in,” Aishia uttered simply.

“That’s dreaming a little too high, there. Baths like the one in the stone house aren’t common in the Strahl region. Isn’t it enough that there’s a bathroom in each room?” Celia asked with a wry smile.

There were bathrooms in the rooms allocated to Rio’s party, too, with a shallow bathtub that allowed for washing up, but they didn’t compare to the bath installed in the stone house. However, bathrooms were already more than enough by Strahl region standards.

“The two of you are completely accustomed to deeper bathtubs, I see,” Rio said with a smile.

“Yup, I like taking baths. Makes me sleepy.” Aishia nodded, speaking softly.

“This girl really falls asleep, you know? I was so surprised when I got in after her,” Celia said tiredly.

“The warmth is comfortable.”

“Geez...” Aishia’s blunt remark made Celia puff up her cheeks slightly.

“Ahaha,” Rio laughed with amusement. From appearances alone, Aishia looked more mature than Celia did, but at times like this it was hard to tell who was older.

Thus, their conversation continued until a waiter knocked on the door to the room and carried in the newest dishes.

“Thank you for waiting. Would you like to select your next drink too?” the employee asked, noticing that there was little alcohol remaining in the decanter.

“Let’s see. Cecilia, would you like to choose the next one? I’m not too familiar with the different makers,” Rio said. Having been raised as a noble, Celia should’ve been more familiar with brands and makers than Rio.

“I’m not very knowledgeable myself...” Celia said as she looked at the menu. “Then how about this house wine, in the same decanter as this, please.” The wine on the front sign of the store seemed to have attracted her attention, as she pointed it out for their order.

“Understood.” The store attendant responded respectfully, leaving without a sound.

“Where was the wine made?” Rio asked.

“Here in Duke Cretia’s territory. It’s a product made in the vineyards of the Ricca Guild. Since it’s a locally made item and all, how about we just sit back and enjoy ourselves?” Celia said, giggling happily.

“Yes, I think that’s a good choice.” Rio nodded with a faint smile. He normally couldn’t help himself from drinking the alcohol made by the spirit folk, but having a Strahl-made drink for once sounded good. All the more so during a time like this when they were living an irregular, luxurious lifestyle.

“The new dishes are also delicious.” Aishia maneuvered her knife and fork elegantly to pick at the newly served dishes while smacking her lips. A gentle mood had settled in the peaceful and refined private room.

“...It sounds kind of noisy out there,” Rio said with a glance at the door. Shouting could be heard down the corridor; it seemed as though someone was arguing. Since the restaurant was so quiet, the slightly raised voices could be heard quite well.

“...Is it a fight?” Celia murmured worriedly. As more time passed, the arguing party seemed to be drawing closer to their room. Then, right on the other side of the door, the aggravated voice of a young man could be heard.

“I’m telling you, I insist on using the private room I had last time. If it’s money, I can pay three times the usual rate.”

“This isn’t a matter of money. The room is currently in use by other customers. We will not ask them to leave,” a man who was most likely an employee of the inn objected firmly.

Judging by the situation, Rio took a guess at what was happening and spoke rather tiredly. “...It sounds like this room may be in demand.”

“What... should we do?” Celia asked, looking at Rio.

“Let’s wait a little longer and see what happens. They could be trying to use a different room, so it would be a little silly to purposely step outside if we were wrong.” Rio’s words were simple as he gave a gentle smile.

“We’re visiting as very important guests. The upper class of this city will hear of this,” A different male voice to the aggravated man said, speaking carefully. His voice also sounded rather young, his tone overbearing. In reality, by dangling their influence, it was clear they were making a threat. Perhaps they were used to things like this.

“...If you’re referring to Lady Liselotte, then please, feel free to appeal to her directly. We are simply following our instructions.” The inn’s employee did not back down.

“...What a stubborn fool. Enough — it’s no use speaking with you. You’d better watch your back later,” the second male said as a final warning.

“As you wish,” the employee replied bluntly.

The aggravated man must have run out of patience, as he spoke up in irritation. “That’s enough, Stewart. We’ll settle this with the other customers ourselves.”

“You may not,” the employee protested, but the angry man’s voice rose loudly.

“Move it. You’re in the way.”

“S-Sir! You cannot do this!” The employee yelled; perhaps he had been pushed out of the way. The quarrel was occurring right outside the room Rio and the others were in. It was almost certain that their room was the one in question.

“...I’ll deal with this. The two of you should ignore them.” Rio sighed with annoyance from the bottom of his heart as he addressed Celia and Aishia. Immediately after that, the door to their room flew open without even a knock.

◇　◇　◇

Stewart Huguenot was Duke Huguenot’s eldest son. With his father the most prominent great lord in the kingdom, he was the prodigal son that had been raised with everything he could ever want.

While he was satisfied with the minimum amount of time his busy father spent with him during his childhood, those around him would praise him endlessly. Even if he caused a little trouble here and there, no one would scold him. But even for someone like Stewart, there were two turning points of his life.

The first was when he was eleven and participated in the outdoor drill at the Royal Academy, during which the incident where Flora nearly fell off the cliff occurred. The blame had been falsely shifted to the orphan, Rio, but it was the first time Stewart had provoked the fierce rage of Duke Huguenot since he was born.

However, contrary to the intense emotions of rage, Duke Huguenot was exceedingly cold. Instead of verbally abusing his son for the failure, he listened to Stewart directly explain the events that happened.

“There will be no next time.”

He’d concluded with those menacing words, his cold gaze mixed with disappointment and contempt.

“Y-Yes, sir!”

It was the first time Stewart felt fear toward his father. At the same time, he realized that he would never be a subject of his father’s familial love. Because Duke Huguenot had not felt anger towards his son, but anger at prioritizing himself over his family. When he had said “There will be no next time,” the duke was declaring that the next time Stewart made a fatal mistake, he would be mercilessly discarded as nothing more than a defective item. To Duke Huguenot, he was no more than a political tool. Stewart finally realized that harsh truth.

Perhaps it was from then onwards that Stewart became more aware of his status in society. While his outward attitude did not change, he was constantly aware of whether he was dealing with people higher or lower than him, constantly checking and clarifying his own status. As a result, Stewart discriminated more against those he believed were below him, while interacting carefully with those he was unsure of or above him.

The second turning point of Stewart’s life was when his father, Duke Huguenot, lost his position. He learned that even his terrifying father could fall... Perhaps he had misjudged their status, or maybe there were other complicated factors that had contributed. Still, when he considered that, Stewart suddenly felt fed up with the life of a noble. There was no way he could change his lifestyle at the age of fifteen, and he had already been raised as a noble accustomed to a certain standard of living.

However, Stewart had no confidence in his ability to behave as Duke Huguenot’s successor well in the future. If there was a successor, it would be his little brother. Some people even believed Duke Huguenot had raised his brother as the main succession candidate.

What a pain in the ass.

When Stewart firmly started to believe that, he appealed to Duke Huguenot to become a knight instead. As a result, his request was accepted readily and he was placed in the elite guard tasked with protecting Flora. It was awkward being with Flora due to their history at the Royal Academy’s outdoor drill, but he wasn’t about to object to any orders from his father.

Thus began Stewart’s life as a knight, but there were rarely any dangerous missions to go around when following royalty like Flora. At most, he would go and exterminate monsters in the name of practical training, and complete escort mission trainings.

However, even then, Stewart’s life was fulfilling. He didn’t need to think about anything when he was swinging his sword at monsters, and it was a good form of stress relief. On top of that, he had a partner in crime in the form of his upperclassman from their academy days, his now-colleague Alphonse Rodan.

Alphonse was the second son of Marquess Rodan, and another stereotypical example of a prodigal son. He was similar to Stewart in the way that he liked to use his status to the maximum degree, doing as he liked. Ever since being appointed into the same elite guard for Flora, Stewart and Alphonse hung out more than ever before. They would eliminate monsters together, eat meals from the same pot, and drink together while grumbling. Recently, they even started polishing their skills in womanizing together, as noble prodigal sons would.

As time progressed, Sakata Hiroaki had become their charge after he’d been summoned, but that had made no significant impacts on Stewart’s life. If he had to pick a bone with something, then it was probably the fact he secretly considered Hiroaki to be intolerable — and detested him, thanks to Hiroaki’s clearly condescending attitude.

Today’s events changed nothing.

The boy named Haruto had suddenly appeared at the scene, slaughtering the powerful minotaurs in front of Liselotte’s attendants, who lavished him with attention, which was understandable. While they weren’t happy having the best part taken away from them, most of the knights present — including Stewart — had shuddered in awe at the sight of how he’d fought. It was the reason why Stewart and Alphonse decided to use that as a topic to approach the beautiful ladies that served Liselotte. And so, after arriving at Amande, the two knights started chatting up the attendant girls in the garden of Liselotte’s estate good-naturedly. Hiroaki must have been listening, as he suddenly interrupted.

“Ah, well. Intruding on another party’s battle and stealing all the limelight isn’t really something to praise.”

Right beside him were Flora and Roanna. The friendly air that Stewart and Alphonse had built up dispersed in an instant.

“Forgive me for asking, great hero, but what do you mean by that?” Despite his irritation, Stewart questioned Hiroaki courteously.

“We were finally fighting with coordination. If a third party slips into the fight without permission, what do you think would happen? Of course the fight wouldn’t go as planned, ruining everything. Well, the one stealing the kills probably thought he was being helpful. If you ask me, it’s bad manners.” Hiroaki sighed in exasperation.

“Hah...” Stewart let out a dumbfounded reply. The first half of that speech aside, he had completely lost track of what Hiroaki was saying partway. There were no manners in a life or death battle with monsters.

“Well, I can understand his feelings of irritation, watching the small fry desperately struggle to fight. Guys who steal kills like that tend to crave attention like, ‘oh my god, look at me, I’m strong right? I’ll lend you a hand!’ It’s an act that steals the opportunity for those already fighting to learn and develop. It spoils the mood, since lots of people hate having their prey snatched from under their nose.” It was a statement that completely insulted the knights that had been on the battlefield. However, Hiroaki didn’t seem to realize that, as he continued to blabber away without pause.

In the end, Roanna had to prompt Hiroaki to move on before he wandered away, ruining the mood for any further discussion as the attendant girls soon took their leave to return to work.

Stewart, in the meantime, headed to the guest facilities allocated to them for the day in displeasure. It was a splendid building directly beside Liselotte’s estate. However, even though there was good food and drink, there were no women. Liselotte’s servants were present, but they weren’t about to make the servants pour their drinks for them.

And so, on this visit to Amande too, Stewart headed out to the city with Alphonse to clear their gloomy moods. While part of the reason was due to his irritation at Hiroaki’s earlier ignorant remark, he had also just gone through a battle of life and death with more monsters than he had ever faced before, leaving his mind and body helplessly worked up.

They headed to a bar targeted towards the wealthy and had a drink and snacks before happily moving on to another bar that specialized in entertainment from women. Having previously visited this store and paid good money, they were remembered as important customers and welcomed warmly, and chose two of the prettier girls among the staff to serve them.

“Well, he’s all talk and attitude. There’s nothing much else to him, really.” They spoke their complaints about someone in particular whilst drinking heartily. Eventually, the name of a famous restaurant in Amande was brought up.

“Yeah, we’ve been to that store before. I can take you there now, if you’d like,” Stewart said, showing off. The girls were completely on board with it, so Stewart and Alphonse left the bar with the girls in high spirits.

However, the situation took a turn once they arrived at the aforementioned restaurant. They’d decided on using the best private room for the occasion, but when he requested the room...

“Our deepest apologies. That room is already in use by another customer. I can prepare another private room for you right away...”

The room Stewart was after was already in use. It was like someone had dumped cold water on him after he’d finally recovered his mood.

“Well, why don’t you show us the other options first?” Alphonse said high-handedly. With that, the male employee lead Stewart’s party inside the shop.

“...I think I want the room I requested after all. Can’t you prepare that instead?” Alphonse insisted unreasonably.

“I’m sorry, that private room is already in use by another customer.”

“Just get them to change rooms. I’ll pay you three times as much.”

“I’m sorry, I cannot do that.” Alphonse picked a fight, but the employee shook his head quietly.

“...Is the room really in use?” Alphonse said, doubting the employee’s words.

“Of course it is,” the man replied, nodding his head curtly. It was at this point that the girls accompanying them started looking concerned. They could tell that the scene was gradually worsening.

“Then I want to see with my own eyes whether it’s actually in use or not.” Perhaps the alcohol in Alphonse’s system gave him a confidence boost, or perhaps he was starting to get irritated at the employee’s resolute attitude, as he started walking with a sullen look.

“H-Hold on a minute, sir!” Naturally, the employee tried to stop him, but Alphonse didn’t waver. He continued his brisk walk forwards to the private room they had used before.

Alphonse’s bad habit is showing again, Stewart thought calmly when Alphonse started bickering with the employee, sobering up a little. It would be humiliating to back down in front of the girls they wanted to impress, so he decided that if worse came to worst, he could just let money handle the situation. Thus, they arrived before their target room, but the girls appeared to be frightened, which wasn’t ideal, obviously.

“We’re visiting as very important guests. The upper class of this city will hear of this,” Stewart said to reassure the girls.

“...If you’re referring to Lady Liselotte, then please, feel free to appeal to her directly. We are simply following our instructions.” The employee’s attitude became even more resolute in response to Stewart’s words.

What? I even prepared a point of compromise for him to accept. Stewart sulked for a moment.

“...What a stubborn fool. Enough — it’s no use speaking with you. You’d better watch your back later,” he found himself saying before he knew it.

“As you wish,” the inn’s employee replied bluntly.

Alphonse must have run out of patience, as he spoke up in irritation. “That’s enough, Stewart. We’ll settle this with the other customers ourselves.”

“You may not,” the employee protested.

“Move it. You’re in the way,” Alphonse declared loudly, forcibly pushing the employee out of the way.

“S-Sir! You cannot do this!” the employee yelled, but Alphonse was already standing before the door to the room, and opened it without knocking.

◇　◇　◇

“...What a commotion.” Rio glanced at the intruders and stood up with a sigh. For a brief moment, Celia took one look at Stewart and Alphonse’s faces and startled, but he didn’t notice.

...Huh? These two? Rio thought oddly. Like with Flora and Roanna, they seemed familiar. For now, he decided to treat them as though they were meeting for the first time.

Stewart and Alphonse were wearing their own clothing instead of their knight uniforms, but it was easy to tell at a glance that their clothes were of nobility. Behind them stood two girls looking idle, both wearing clothes that were stylish but slightly flashy.

The employee that had been shoved aside by Alphonse belatedly rushed into the room. At the same time, he turned to Rio’s party and bowed his head in a panic. “M-My deepest apologies, sir!”

“Could you explain what’s going on here?” Rio responded in a flat tone.

“Hm? You’re...” Stewart seemed to realize something, narrowing his eyes suspiciously.

“...!” Celia flinched with her whole body, immediately ducking her head down. Stewart and Alphonse were two of her former students — she was worried that they might have recognized her true identity.

“Aren’t you that Haruto guy?” Stewart stared at Rio and asked.

“...I’m sorry, and who might you be?” Rio returned curiously.

“Ah, forgive me. My knowledge of you was one-sided. I am Stewart Huguenot, and this is Alphonse Rodan. If I told you that we are knights from the group you saved today, would that ring a bell?” Stewart introduced himself smoothly as he studied Rio’s face.

“...Is that so? My apologies for the rudeness.” Rio tipped his head lightly in a show of politeness. Hearing their names had completely triggered his memories of the two. There was no way he could’ve forgotten, since this man was the root of all evil behind the false accusation placed on his head. Alphonse was his former classmate, too.

“No, that’s fine,” Stewart gloated with a smug huff. While things had taken a slightly troublesome turn, if the boy wasn’t a stranger to his family background, then everything would work out, Stewart thought confidently.

“...” In reality, the attendant seemed to be at a loss for what to do, seeing Rio and Stewart being acquainted already. The girls who had come along with them were also looking at Stewart in awe.

This is rather strange, Rio thought. “So, what brings you to this room?” he asked, just in case.

“We wanted to use this room.” Alphonse cut to the chase.

“This exact room?”

Alphonse’s declaration was so bold, Rio couldn’t help but react in shock. Upon closer inspection, Alphonse’s face was red: it was clear he was drunk.

This is why drunks are such a pain... No, not drunks. High and mighty nobles. Rio held back the urge to sigh and chose to leave quietly instead. It would be too much of a bother to deal with these two any longer.

“We had just finished eating ourselves. Please, feel free to come in,” Rio said, sending a message to Celia and Aishia seated at the table behind him with a casual look. Aishia and Celia nodded silently and stood up.

“Wh...” It was at this point that Stewart and the others finally noticed Celia and Aishia. When they spotted the beauty of the girls, they couldn’t help but gulp.

“Come here, you two.” Rio guided Celia over, then stood as a wall between them and Stewart’s group. They briskly tried to make their way out of the room.

“Hey, hold on a minute,” Alphonse called out.

“Yes?” Rio replied, directly in the firing line.

“Let’s compromise. Why don’t you join us for a meal and drinks?” Alphonse extended a hand in invitation while looking at Aishia and Celia.

“While we are very grateful for the offer, we have unfortunately already finished eating and drinking,” Rio said, shaking his head bluntly.

“Oh? You’re rejecting our invitation?” Alphonse asked in a bold tone.

“I apologize. It has been a long journey here.” Rio’s answer did not change. While his words were courteous, his approach to rejection was firm.

“I see. I can’t say I’m impressed at how you’re rejecting a noble’s invitation. You may be skilled at the sword, but you’re still a commoner, no? Isn’t that right, Stewart?” Alphonse said with condemnation, turning to Stewart for backup.

After a short pause, Stewart nodded and looked towards Aishia and Celia. “...Yes, I suppose I do agree.” He figured Rio was staying at this inn as Liselotte’s savior and guest, so he didn’t think it would be smart to act too strongly before him. However, he also thought it’d be a shame if Aishia and Celia were to depart like this.

“I ask for your leniency.” Rio showed no sign of faltering at their roundabout threats and shook his head respectfully, moving to take his leave.

“Hey, hold on. You can’t gain social position through your sword hand alone. It’d be a shame, what with skills as wonderful as yours. Don’t you have some interest in climbing up in the world? Depending on your attitude, we could put in a good word for you to become a knight.” Alphonse was also a stubborn man, and flaunted gains to attempt at some level of negotiation.

“I’m fine as is. And I am tired, so if you’d excuse me.” Rio continued to shake his head bluntly. Sensing that the atmosphere had turned sour once again, the two girls that had accompanied Stewart and Alphonse shrunk back into the corner.

“Sir, if you bother our other customers any more than this, I’m afraid we will have to respond appropriately on our part too...” The male employee’s face had also grown pale, but even he felt the need to intervene here and gave a warning to keep them in check.

“Alphonse, I think this is eno...” Stewart tried to warn. While it would result in utterly destroying their reputation, he turned to self-preservation as things started to get out of hand.

“...No, hold on. I’ll try one last time. At the very least, how about those two stay with us instead? How about it, girls?” Alphonse seemed to be past the point of no return, desperately holding back his irritation as he addressed Aishia and Celia in a gentleman-like manner.

“...” However, both Aishia and Celia held their silence and ignored him like Rio had told them to. “Kuh...” Alphonse must have considered this a great humiliation, as his face twisted greatly.

“Now, if that was all you needed. We shall take our leave...” Rio sighed flatly, giving Celia and Aishia a gentle nudge in the back to move them out of the room. On their way past the male employee, he leaned in to whisper, “I’m sorry for the commotion. Oh, and there is no need to report this to Lady Liselotte either, if you so wish.”

It was the least he could offer in gratitude for the employee’s attempts at protecting them. He didn’t want him to feel responsible over such a ridiculous matter.

“M-My deepest apologies!” The employee bowed his head in a fluster. He had been given strict orders from Aria to treat Liselotte’s savior with the utmost hospitality, yet this had happened. Meanwhile, Stewart’s face darkened uncomfortably as he realized their mistake, while in contrast, Alphonse allowed his rage to completely consume him.

“...Hey, wait,” he muttered furiously, but Rio did not stop walking.

“I told you to wait!” Alphonse finally yelled. He stood before the door, blocking their path.

“Yes?”

At Rio’s nonplussed question, Alphonse glared at him with hostility. “You dare insult me?”

“A-Alphonse!” Stewart hurriedly tried to stop Alphonse, but he ignored Stewart’s attempt at restraint and flared up at Rio.

“It seems you don’t know how to behave before a noble.”

Instead of considering his options logically, his humiliated emotions were completely leading the way. Being born and raised as the son of a high-ranked noble meant he had never needed to learn how to control his temper as a child, making him easier to anger.

“Unfortunately, I was born as a commoner, so I do not. Have I unknowingly done something to offend you?” Rio cocked his head curiously. While his choice of words were polite, his phrasing was provocative. It was the ultimate move of superficial manners.

Celia saw through that side of Rio and made a worried face out of nervousness. Aishia grabbed her hand and squeezed it.

“Ha... Hahaha... I never expected a mere commoner to make this much of a fool out of me. I see you think so highly of yourself, with your common sword and common women. But I can use my right to strike at any moment, you do realize?” Alphonse said with a twitching smile. The right to strike was a special privilege for nobility that allowed them to kill when their honor was compromised.

“Oh my. I’ve heard that the requisites for the right to strike can be extremely severe depending on national or territorial laws. Which requisite have I fulfilled in dishonoring you?” I’d like to see you try, was what Rio was strongly implying. The requisites for right to strike were to be investigated after the action was performed, but if Alphonse tried to declare he was dishonored by being ignored when flirting with girls while drunk, he’d be completely ridiculed.

Not to mention the fact Amande was under Liselotte’s governing. It would be one thing if they were within the Kingdom of Beltrum where Alphonse had influence, but there was no way that nonsense would be accepted in another country.

That being said, a commoner with no knowledge of how the right to strike worked would have cowered in fear by now, yet Rio did not falter an inch.

“Guh...” Having the faults in his request so easily raised had Alphonse glaring at Rio hatefully. Even he knew he was at a logical disadvantage. However, his haughty pride wouldn’t allow him to back down to a mere commoner after being humiliated so much already.

“Have you had enough yet?” Rio could no longer hide his exasperation in his question to Alphonse.

Alphonse stared at Rio sharply. Out of the blue, he lunged forward at Rio with his fist held high. “Shut the hell up, you lowly commoner!”

“Kyaa!” Celia screamed from behind Rio. He couldn’t avoid him by stepping to the side, nor could he step backwards, either.

Thus, Rio engaged with Alphonse from head-on. After grasping the arm that had been raised in a punch, he gracefully pinned Alphonse down to the ground.

“Ow!” Alphonse cried out, the pain unbearable.

“Wha...?!” Stewart’s gaze was stolen by how skilful Rio’s restraint techniques were. He had no idea what movement was taken just now to restrain Alphonse so well.

“A-Alphonse! Hey, you! Release him!” Stewart objected, having returned to his senses after a moment. In that time, Aishia took the chance to pull Celia’s hand and place distance between themselves and Rio.

“I’m afraid I must object to that. If I release him, he’ll attack me right away.” It’s legitimate self-defense, Rio thought flatly.

“S-Shut up!” Rio’s response seemed to have touched a nerve, as Stewart tried to grab at him. At that, Rio swiftly stood up and evaded Stewart’s hand, and as a result, Stewart’s momentum caused him to stumble over his feet.

“Grr...!” He corrected his balance immediately, now glaring at Rio angrily. The now-released Alphonse also struggled to his feet.

“You’ve done it now, you bastard!” Alphonse yelled, lunging again to punch him. However, Rio evaded his fist lightly, all while barely moving from his spot.

“Kuh!” Alphonse completely snapped, continuing to swing his fist. Rio finally had enough and sighed in exasperation, slapping away Alphonse’s fist. Then, he grabbed Alphonse’s arm and twisted it while standing up.

“Gwah?!” Alphonse’s face twisted.

“Alphonse? Wha?!” Stewart tried to jump to his rescue, hurriedly grabbing Rio. However, Rio shoved Alphonse’s body away, sending the two of them falling over each other dramatically.

“Guh...” Everyone other than Aishia averted their eyes at the pitiful scene.

As a result, silence fell over the room. During that time, Rio silently moved his body, approaching where Stewart and Alphonse had fallen over each other. He pushed them both down from above, easily restraining them.

“Guh, hey!”

“What do you think you’re doing?! Let go, dammit!”

Stewart and Alphonse complained in an unsightly way, but Rio paid them no heed. He continued to restrain them without letting his guard down.

However, he couldn’t remain in this position forever. Rio sighed in annoyance before addressing the employee, who was standing still in a daze. “Unfortunately, it doesn’t seem like this can be settled peacefully after all. Could you please call someone here who can deal with these two appropriately?”

Chapter 5: Evils Lurking Near

Meanwhile, when Rio was dining together with Liselotte at her estate, by her invitation...

Alphonse Rodan had apologized to Rio, split ways with Stewart Huguenot, and was visiting the forests to the west of Amande with a few other knights.

Alphonse was currently walking along the road to the west; his goal was to, of course, investigate the cause of the huge spawns of monsters and confirm that no more savage monsters lurked in the woods. In other words, a reconnaissance in force. At the request of Duke Huguenot, an advance party was formed consisting of mostly knights traveling together with them, which he was made to join on their mission.

Incidentally, Stewart was confined to house arrest on Duke Huguenot’s order, remaining at the mansion. The fact he gave Alphonse a chance to clear his name but not his own son was probably because he had showed consideration for Marquess Rodan’s house.

Fuck this! I’ll never forget this — I’ll never forgive this! Making me lose face like this... Alphonse was holding an irrational, deep-set grudge. Rio, Duke Huguenot, Aishia, Celia, Liselotte, Aria... he couldn’t help but feel so much hatred for all the factors that stood in the way of what he wanted.

Why did I have to apologize to that filthy commoner anyway?! He was completely shelving the fact he had caused the problem, though he may have never considered it a problem to begin with, being that he thought he was a human of the privileged class.

Commoners should just shut the hell up and do as we say. Those women, too — they should have been grateful we bothered to lay our eyes on them. Getting ahead of themselves for looking a little attractive... Alphonse’s rage did not calm. In the time between bowing at Rio’s feet and moving to the forest, he had continuously simmered in his anger.

Of course, his apology had been for appearances only. Even if it was only in appearance, he had showed intent to apologize with his behavior. Duke Huguenot’s intervention meant a settlement contract had been formed.

Alphonse could no longer touch Rio and the others. In other words — he had been utterly defeated. On top of that, Duke Huguenot had stamped him as an incompetent person.

Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck! I’m not at fault! I’m not incompetent! Alphonse couldn’t forgive the current situation. A high class and talented individual like him could not accept the fact he was being outright rejected by society.

...First is that damn duke. Just watch, you old fool. I’ll show you what I’m worth. A strong desire to prove himself was welling up within Alphonse right alongside his rage. He wanted to prove Duke Huguenot wrong so much, he could barely stand it.

I’ll definitely achieve something here. Alphonse harbored his ambitions with eagerness. He had been glaring around at the surrounding forest, searching for a target to vent his bitterness against.

“Oi, Alphonse. You’ve been restless for a while now. I get that you’re annoyed at being scolded, but we’re mid-mission right now. Get your head in the zone.” The commanding knight of the investigation squad was unable to ignore Alphonse’s clearly bad mood and gave him a warning.

“Tch,” Alphonse clicked his tongue. The commanding knight was in his mid-twenties, normally acting as the vice-commander of Flora’s elite guards, but Alphonse’s family was higher-ranked. Any speech from a person of lower social status would only fall upon Alphonse’s deaf ears at the moment.

“...Hey, I don’t like your attitude.” The commanding knight frowned. Even if Alphonse was from a better house, he was the superior rank military-wise, and proud of obtaining his position through his own ability.

“That wasn’t my intention. I’m just on edge from my hatred of monsters. More importantly, how long are we going to walk along this road for? Let’s go into the forest already.” Alphonse huffed with a rebellious attitude.

“...We are merely an advance party dispatched to strengthen guard patrol. Reconnaissance in force is part of our mission, but our goal is not to exterminate monsters,” the commanding knight replied in an unhappy voice.

At that, the knights that had formed lines while on guard of their surrounding started being distracted by Alphonse and the commander’s conversation.

“You say that, but what if a minotaur appears in the city?” Alphonse objected with a more aggressive attitude than usual.

“Cut that out already. That’s why we’re currently strengthening the city’s security. It’s not something for a mere foot soldier like you to worry about. You just follow your orders,” the commanding knight scolded Alphonse a bit harshly.

“Hmph, what a coward...” Alphonse muttered quietly.

The commanding knight finally seemed to snap, arguing back aggressively. “And here I was being considerate, since you’re clearly still a child. Would you like to head into the forest alone instead? You may be able to encounter a minotaur, as you seem to wish.”

“Kuh...” Alphonse frowned deeply. No matter how hot-headed he was getting because of anger, he wasn’t foolish enough to think he could defeat a minotaur alone.

“That will be unnecessary.” From out of nowhere, an unfamiliar man’s voice echoed loudly.

“Who’s there?!” The knights looked around them in a hurry. Two men appeared from the forest, stepping onto the road. One was Reiss, wearing a black hood to cover his appearance, and the other boldly had his face on full display. The man with his face revealed looked to be in his prime adult years, a sword hanging from his waist and in an outfit fitting for a mercenary. His name was Lucius. While his facial features were refined, he emitted a wild aura filled with confidence and spirit.

“There are no monsters in the forest right now,” Lucius said, approaching the knights without hesitation. Once he was within ten meters of the knights, the commanding knight shouted an order in a stern voice.

“Freeze!”

“Yeah, yeah.” Lucius did as he was told.

“Are you an adventurer of Amande?” the commanding knight asked.

“Nope, that I am not.” Lucius shook his head casually.

“...How suspicious. Then what were you doing in the forest?” The knights fixed their dubious gazes on Reiss, who was standing behind Lucius.

“Why, being suspicious people, of course. And would you lot be the knights from the Kingdom of Beltrum?”

“...How do you know that?” Lucius’ question made the knights all the more wary at once.

“Well, there is only one group of knights staying in Amande right now, after all. The elite knights escorting Princess Flora, that is.”

When Flora’s name came up, the knights expressions became even more grim. “...Who the hell are you?”

“I have a little business with you lot. Seems like there’s about twenty of you. And all youths, at that.” Lucius smiled with extreme cheerfulness, looking around at the knights.

“Come to think of it, you were a former noble of Beltrum, weren’t you? Are there any faces you recognize?” Reiss asked from behind Lucius.

“Nope. But it wouldn’t change a thing if there was.”

“That’s good to hear. Their bodies will be satisfactory, so I’m counting on you,” Reiss said in a flat voice.

“What a pain. Should we just mess them up a bit and restrain them?” Alphonse drew his sword. It was the perfect opponent to take his irritation out on.

“Wait, I want to talk to them some more...” The commanding knight tried to continue with his interrogation, but —

“Hahaha, there’s a lively one among them. How nice.” Lucius looked at Alphonse’s face and laughed joyfully.

“Make sure you don’t kill them. Healing is troublesome, so don’t detach their limbs, either,” Reiss said tiredly to Lucius.

“I’m helping you out... At least let me have a little fun. You just make sure no one runs away,” Lucius replied apathetically, drawing a sinister, jet-black sword from its sheath at his waist.

“The other side seems ready to go. Let me take him on.” Alphonse grinned smugly, stepping forth to fight.

“...No. Surround and capture them. If he resists, I don’t mind if you counterattack, but...” The commanding officer chose to respond with only rationality. Since they knew about the knights and Flora, he wanted to talk to them a little more.

“?!”

Suddenly, Lucius broke into a run. His unbelievable speed left the knights wide-eyed in surprise.

“Brace...!” The commanding officer tried to give his order in a fluster. However, Lucius had snuck into the midst of the knights in an instant.

“Too slow! You should have strengthened yourselves with magic the moment I drew my sword.”

“Guh...” One of the knights went flying through the air, kicked away by Lucius. The knights around them looked upon that scene with their jaws dropped.

“A-Aaaah!” Alphonse roared in anger, charging straight to slash Lucius. His mouth was turned upwards in a savage smile, the opportunity perfect for him to expend his stress.

“Hahaha, you sure are an interesting one.” Lucius blocked Alphonse’s sword and laughed heartily.

“Die! Augendae Corporis!” Alphonse used physical ability enchanting magic as he put more strength into his sword. The spell circle appeared just a moment later, making strength swell within him and helping him push his sword forward with force. However, Lucius took a graceful step backwards and retreated.

“I’ll leave you until last. Come on now, how about you lot activate your enhancement magic too?” Lucius said to Alphonse, before provoking the other knights into action.

“Kuh, Augendae Corporis!” The knights, in anger, each enhanced their physical abilities with magic one by one.

“Fine, kill that one! Just leave the hooded man instead!” the commanding knight said, having finally considered Lucius’ killing intent.

“Yeah, give it your best shot!” Lucius shouted, jumping into the group of knights himself. Of course, the knights swung their swords to slay Lucius. However, Lucius slipped through the swinging slashing swords, enjoying the thrill.

“What’s the matter, huh?! Is this all you can do?! Entertain me more!”

“D-Damn it!”

The knights felt like they were hallucinating, cutting through nothing but fog. No matter how many times they swung their swords, despite being certain they would make contact, their blades could not reach Lucius.

Lucius swung his sword, pulling it back at the last moment before it could kill any of the knights. Occasionally, when the knights thought he was attacking, he would just deflect their attacks and do nothing else.

This guy’s toying with us! the knights concluded as Lucius laughed cheerfully at them. There was no doubt Lucius was insane, genuinely enjoying this situation of slipping through the flashes of swords.

Time passed like that until Lucius spoke up, his tone full of boredom. “Ah... Guess it’s time to lower the numbers.” The end of his sword drove into the solar plexus of a knight, making him groan in agony.

“Guh!”

“Now it’s my turn to attack,” Lucius laughed brightly and began his counterattack.

“Gah!”

“Hah...”

He struck two knights with his fist and foot, making them collapse on the ground. No sooner had he done that, the next knight was being blown back by Lucius, flying through the air in a dramatic fashion. It was as though Lucius could read the movements of the knights completely, aiming for their weak points, moving before they could respond, and reaping them of their consciousness one by one with his blows.

“N-No way...” Alphonse watched his colleagues get taken down helplessly and found himself frozen in shock, before he suddenly returned to his senses and looked around. Their overwhelmingly advantageous situation had been flipped in an instant. Even at this moment, the number of knights that were safe was dwindling.

At that moment, Alphonse felt their defeat at hand — at this rate, they would lose. As he came to that realization, another knight, then another, fell to the ground.

“Wow, it sure is easier to move around when the numbers have decreased. I can go even faster now!” Lucius moved even faster than before, with no rhyme or reason to his actions. His speed was faster than that of the knights that had enhanced their physical abilities with magic.

That movement... An enchanted sword! Alphonse thought, inferring the reason as to why Lucius’ physical abilities were far beyond the norm. There was only one way he could have moved faster than their magically-enhanced selves.

Enchanted swords this, enchanted swords that! It’s unfair! If I had one too, I could’ve...! As someone without one, Alphonse felt deep envy, as unproductive and meaningless an emotion as it was to have at the moment. The likelihood of him escaping was growing smaller by the minute.

“Guh!” Struck by a knee blow, another knight fell to the ground.

“Ah, four more left,” Lucius said, looking over the cleared view of the road. Over twenty experienced knights had been reduced to four in less than a minute.

I-Impossible... Alphonse thought in a daze. When he looked around, the only people who were still conscious and on their feet were the four knights — including him and the commanding officer — as well as Lucius and Reiss.

“Thanks to you, I’ve made much progress in retrieving the unconscious knights,” Reiss was observing Lucius and the knights from a small distance away, having gathered all the knights Lucius defeated without anyone’s realization. They were all out cold.

“One last job left, it seems. It’ll be your turn soon too, yeah?” Lucius said, looking at Alphonse, who had completely lost the will to fight.

“Eek...” Alphonse backed away reflexively in fear. No, it wasn’t only Alphonse; the other remaining knights had lost their will to fight as well, inching backwards away from Lucius.

“R-Run! Retreat!” the still unharmed commanding officer yelled. Immediately, the four knights — including Alphonse — broke into a run down the road.

I-It’s for help! I need to call for help! This is just a strategic retreat! Alphonse told himself as he desperately ran. There was no trace of the enthusiastic spirit he had when he wanted to take down a minotaur to clear his name.

“Did none of you see our difference in physical abilities when I was fighting? Hey! Even if you run, I’ll just catch up to you!” Lucius said in a voice filled with scorn before kicking off from the ground and chasing the knights. The distance between them closed in an instant, but the desperate knights didn’t realize it.

“Hah, hah...!” Alphonse panted, focusing solely on moving his feet. Eventually, a sword reached out from behind him, passing a hair’s breadth away from his cheek.

“E-Eeeh?! Wah!” Unable to press on any further, Alphonse stepped to the side and haphazardly swung his sword at Lucius, but his sword slashed through the air in vain. “Wha?!”

Alphonse’s eyes widened in shock. Lucius was standing ten meters behind Alphonse, a wicked grin on his face. He watched Alphonse as he kicked the commanding officer.

I-Impossible! His sword was right there! Did he fall back to that position in an instant?! Alphonse’s eyes widened in astonishment as he touched his cheek where the cold sensation of a sword had touched his skin moments earlier.

“You’re the last, as promised. Don’t give me too much trouble,” Lucius quipped tiredly.

“G-Guh...” Unable to say anything in return, Alphonse backed away slowly. He glared at Lucius with deep hatred, as though he was looking upon something that spooked him.

“...You really do have quite the look in your eyes.” Lucius stared back into Alphonse’s eyes and swiftly walked over to close the distance between them. Alphonse shrunk back, unable to move.

“W-What?” There was nowhere to run anymore. Even as Alphonse replied to Lucius, he was groping for a path of survival.

“It’s those eyes of yours that show sly cunning. You may or may not be the one,” Lucius grinned, his words full of meaning.

“H-Huh?” Alphonse mumbled, having no idea what he meant.

“Well. In any case, I’ve become bored. Let’s end this, shall we?”

When Lucius closed the distance further, Alphonse yelled out in a fluster. “W-Wait! If it’s money you want, I’ll pay you. I’ll even stay quiet about you guys!”

“Ah? Money?” Alphonse seemed to pique Lucius’ interest, as he stopped moving forward and grinned in delight.

A-All right! It looks like I can negotiate with money! Seeing the space for negotiation made Alphonse grin in response.

“...You really are an interesting guy,” Lucius huffed through his nose, approaching Alphonse once more.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, at the governor of Amande’s estate, Rio had just finished his meal with Liselotte and was about to leave. Liselotte and the others had come to the garden to say goodbye.

“It’s an honor to be seen off by everyone. Thank you very much for everything today.” Rio drew his right hand over his chest and bowed his head at those present in respect.

“Thank you for coming over today. I’ll send a messenger on another day in the future, so it would be lovely if you could stay in Amande a little longer. Of course, if you need anything, you are free to visit my estate at any time,” Liselotte offered respectfully.

Rio gave a friendly smile as he nodded. “Yes, I appreciate your offer.” Unexpected events had happened one after another, but all’s well that ends well, after all. Thanks to everything, he had been able to form a close friendship with Liselotte.

For the record, defeating the minotaurs to save Liselotte and Flora was considered such a meritorious deed, they had yet to decide what to reward Rio with, requiring more time to examine the case. It was decided that he would visit Liselotte’s mansion again in the future about the matter. In other words, they would continue to be friends from here on out. Both Rio and Liselotte had the same intentions of forming a friendship, but neither of them had a grasp of their distance yet, so they were slowly building a relationship of trust without rushing. It was a bit roundabout, but this was normal for noble negotiations.

“U-Umm...!” Flora took a step forward nervously, calling out to Rio.

“Yes?” Rio replied, tilting his head.

“Umm. If we have the chance to meet again, please feel free to chat with me some more. We also want to give you our gratitude formally, so, please,” Flora said, bowing her head at Rio hesitantly.

“...Yes, it’d be my pleasure.” Rio paused for a moment before nodding with a smile.

Has she noticed something about me after all? Or is this just how she is?

He had suspicions. Flora seemed to be acting strangely, as though she was vaguely trying to meet him halfway. If there was a reason for Flora to be investigating Rio, then the most natural line of reasoning would be because she suspected Haruto was actually Rio. However, as far as he had seen from Flora’s actions until now, he couldn’t say for certain that she doubted him. At the very least, he couldn’t detect any negative feelings, and there was certainly the possibility of this being how Flora would normally interact with him.

Rio had no points of contact with Flora during his time at the academy, so he didn’t actually know what her personality was. All he knew was that she didn’t seem to be a very extroverted person.

I guess I’ll just see how things go for now.

He couldn’t afford to seem too cautious in front of her. It would be best to remain as natural as possible, in order to play innocent, being that there was no proof that he was Rio.

Hiroaki, who had been watching the exchange between Rio and Flora fixedly, spoke up. “Well, we’ll be staying in Amande until the safety of the area is confirmed, too. If you visit Liselotte’s estate, there should be an opportunity to meet again,” he said with a shrug.

“Yes — it’s as the hero says. Oh, that’s right! Sir Haruto prepares tea very well. I had some today by chance, but I could prepare a tea party for us sometime, if you are willing?” Liselotte said.

Rio nodded courteously. “Yes. I would be happy to attend if you wish to invite me.”

“Y-Yes, I would also love to,” Flora agreed nervously.

“Then let’s leave this tea party for another date and wrap this up. Don’t drag this out any longer and let him go home already,” Hiroaki said bluntly.

“You’re right — We shouldn’t keep him any longer. Sir Haruto. Let us meet again,” Duke Huguenot said.

“Yes. Everyone, let us meet another day. Please excuse me.” Rio bowed his head deeply before turning on his heel and walking off. He continued walking to the gate while Liselotte watched his back.

Time to go back to the inn and relax. Freed from acting social with the nobles, Rio let out a small sigh.

◇　◇　◇

Back in the forest to the west of Amande. Rustle, rustle.

Alphonse was vaguely aware that he was being dragged somewhere, that someone had a hold of him by the scruff of his neck. However, he had no idea what was happening. Looking back on his memories, he remembered he had been scouring the forest as part of an investigation.

Ah, shit... Belatedly, he recalled the numerous humiliations he faced afterwards. A surge of anger went through him; he couldn’t forgive anyone who humiliated him.

However... rustle, rustle.

Someone was yanking Alphonse along, making him quite uncomfortable.

Who is it, treating me so roughly? Ugh... Alphonse found it most unpleasant, but a dull pain in the back of his head made him frown.

My head hurts.

Did he hit it hard somewhere? He didn’t know.

“Yo, I’m done,” a man’s voice echoed happily. Immediately after, Alphonse felt the sensation of soaring through the air, before falling to the ground with a heavy thump.

“Ugh...” It seemed he had been thrown. Alphonse groaned.

“Good work. There were so many of them so I’ve already started,” a vacant male voice echoed.

At that point, Alphonse’s mind finally snapped to, and he opened his eyes faintly. He noticed they were inside the forest, having left the road.

This is... Alphonse finally remembered the identities of the men beside him. The ones that had attacked them. Lucius and Reiss.

Reiss was crouched on the ground, working away at something. Beside him stood Lucius.

“They sure are a creepy bunch, as always,” Lucius said, looking to the side. Contrary to his words, a delighted smile was on his face. Alphonse followed Lucius’ gaze.

“Wha...” The scene that met Alphonse’s eyes was so shocking, his body trembled. He could feel his mind reeling instantly.

T-Those are the humanoid monsters that attacked us on the road yesterday! Why are they wearing the elite knights’ uniforms?!

Dark-skinned revenants wearing the same knight uniform as Alphonse stood around in swarms. All the revenants were hairless, their facial structures lacking individuality. However, there was no sign of the savagery witnessed in the ones from yesterday, all of them staring into space with vacant eyes.

What’s the meaning of this?! Alphonse’s mind couldn’t keep up.

“Oh, it looks like someone’s awake.” Reiss looked at Alphonse with a truly wicked smile.

“Tch...!” Alphonse trembled with a flinch.

“I held back a little on this one. Here, have a look.” Lucius chuckled with a grin, grabbing Alphonse’s head and lifting it up. His gaze was led to where Reiss was crouched and beyond.

“Ugh...?!”

Alphonse’s fellow knight was lying there; seeing him made Alphonse’s face twist. There was something wrong with him.

“Ah, ah!” The knight was giving small, soundless screams as his body gave abrupt, twitching jerks. Reiss was holding down the knight from above, his mouth curved into a creepy grin.

“Oh my, is this too much for you to witness? He’s just about to transform.”

As he did so, the knight’s body shook violently.

“W-What did you do?! What is that?!” Alphonse asked in agitation. The person who had once been Alphonse’s colleague was, at that moment, rapidly transforming into a non-human lifeform.

All the hair fell out of his body, his skin darkening in color, audibly hardening in texture. Though it was wearing his knight uniform, it was undoubtedly a revenant. There were absolutely no traces of his former form left. If Alphonse hadn’t known who it used to be before, he wouldn’t have been able to identify it.

“Remodeling the human body. A recreation of the soul and flesh. However, to remodel while they’re still conscious makes them struggle tremendously, so it’s more effective to recreate them while they’re knocked out,” Reiss answered in a somewhat cheerful voice.

“...Uh, hnngh!” The evil was too much for Alphonse to bear, making him feel nauseous.

Reiss, meanwhile, ignored Alphonse. “Ah, Lucius, could you please strip them of their clothes? We don’t want to leave any evidence that the original bodies of the revenants were humans.”

“No way, I have no interest in stripping dudes of their clothes. Do it yourself later.”

Reiss shook his head in disapproval. “Good grief.”

“Nngah... hah...” Alphonse was coughing violently, gasping for breath.

Reiss watched him. “So, why is he still conscious?”

“Test it out on him — your final form of the revenants. I reckon he has the qualities for it,” Lucius answered with a grin.

“It’d be a waste of a body and materials if it fails, though. Body aside, the gems used as materials are valuable, you realize? The chances of succeeding at the final form are low as well.”

“Just this one time is fine, isn’t it? You’re gonna make the rest of the guys here into the enhanced model, no? If you add all the pieces in your hand together, its plenty of power to attack Amande with.”

“...I suppose that’s true.” Reiss stood up with a small sigh. Leaving the newly-completed revenant behind him, he approached Alphonse.

“There we go.” With a carefree word of encouragement, Lucius pinned Alphonse’s arms behind his back and made him stand up.

“L-Let go! Don’t come any closer! Stop! You monster!” Alphonse struggled as he yelled, eyes never leaving the monster that was his former colleague. However, he was unable to break free from Lucius’ abnormal strength.

“Let’s have a look.” Reiss stood before Alphonse. At some point, he picked up an eerie jewel-like stone in his hand, its size the same as a fist.

“Guh?!” The stone was thrust into Alphonse’s chest like piercing through water, and he couldn’t hold back his groan. Yet despite the strange, foreign sensation, there was no pain.

“It doesn’t hurt, right? That’s because I’m not harming your physical body,” Reiss explained cheerfully, his hand in Alphonse’s chest. He leaned in to whisper into Alphonse’s ear. “Both your body and soul will start to hurt from here.”

“Guh... hah...” Alphonse gasped in agony. His heart was hot, his body was hot, and it felt like he was going to melt. He was hit with the urge to spit out everything inside his body, but he wasn’t able to.

“This will take some time.” They were crueler than the verdict of a demon declaring death.

Chapter 8: Daybreak Rondo

While Alphonse was punching Hiroaki in the face, Rio and the others were being escorted to Liselotte’s mansion by the soldiers on hand. The sight of Liselotte bustling about the garden to give orders soon came into view.

“Lady Liselotte, I have brought Sir Haruto and his two companions,” the soldier called, hurrying to report to Liselotte.

“...Haruto, I can feel the unpleasant presence of monsters from that mansion.” Aishia muttered, staring directly at the mansion with a severe look.

“Eh?” Rio followed her gaze, but there was only silence around the mansion. There was no sign of any commotion going on around there, and neither Liselotte nor those around her seemed particularly bothered.

Liselotte came running over to Rio. “Sir Haruto, I’m glad to see you and your two companions are safe.”

“Yes, somehow...” Rio replied in slight confusion.

“I heard you stopped the monsters at the east gate until reinforcements could arrive. Thank you very much for that. Unfortunately, though I would still like to talk to you more, this is an emergency situation. You’ll be safe inside the mansion, so please come this way. I shall lead you.” Liselotte must have been in a rush, as she immediately tried to lead Rio and the girls to the mansion.

“...Did any monsters sneak in here?” Rio asked with a serious look.

“Are you referring to the humanoid monsters? I did hear that some managed to get into the city, but with your assistance, my attendants were able to put an end to them outside the ramparts. I haven’t received any reports from the soldiers patrolling the ramparts of anything otherwise, either...” Liselotte answered, looking at Rio’s expression curiously.

“I... see.” Rio frowned with a troubled look. Even if he told her there were monsters in the mansion, she didn’t have any reason to believe him. There was no knowing if she’d believe him even if he explain Aishia’s background too.

“...Is there something you are concerned with?” Liselotte asked, sensing something was up.

“Yes, there seems to be a strange aura coming from the mansion. Is there anyone inside?”

“The hero and Princess Flora have taken refuge inside, and their knights are guarding them. I’ll send a servant to confirm.” Just as Liselotte suggested that, a tremendous booming sound echoed from the mansion.

“Kya?!” Celia and Liselotte couldn’t help but scream.

“That’s...” Rio immediately directed his gaze at the source of the sound. A giant hole had opened in the wall of the second floor, and a torrent of water poured out from it.

“W-What?!” Liselotte said in shock. At that very moment, a hooded Lucius came bursting out of the mansion’s front door in a rush.

“Hahaha, coming through!” Kicking and struggling over his shoulder was none other than Flora.

“Let go of me! Ah, there are monsters inside! Roanna, and the hero! Someone, please save them!” Flora said incoherently. She had been trying to escape the hold restraining her when she’d noticed the allies around her.

“Didn’t I say I’d cut your legs off if you struggled?” Lucius hit the back of Flora’s legs with the side of his hand in a karate chop. Since Flora was being carried facing backwards, she mistook the sensation for a blade and let out a frightened squeak.

Liselotte couldn’t understand why Flora was being carried like that, but she clearly sensed there was something bad about the situation and gave an order on the spot. “Someone apprehend that man!”

“Nope! Too slow! The princess is mine! Try if you want, but you ain’t getting her back!” The speed with which Lucius was running was abnormal. He burst out of the estate grounds before the formation surrounding him was even completed. It was as though he was enjoying the chase. Meanwhile, Rio reacted to Lucius’ voice, eyes widening intensely.

“Could that voice be...?”

Rio’s heart thudded in his chest. It was similar to the low tone of the man’s voice that grated on his ears... A voice he would never forget. Rio wanted to run after him right away, but waves of pale black revenants were swarming out of the mansion’s front door.

“Graaargh!” The revenants started attacking the people nearby indiscriminately, and pandemonium fell upon the garden in an instant. Furthermore, from the hole in the wall of the mansion appeared another, pitch black revenant — Alphonse.

“Hmph.” Alphonse leapt down and glanced over the scene in the garden. He snorted.

“Kshaaa!” One of the rampaging revenants suddenly attacked Rio’s group.

Rio drew his sword in a flash, thrusting it through the heart of the approaching revenant. “Gwah?!” it cried out.

“...The three of you should stand back.” Rio said to Celia and the others behind him as his eyes followed Lucius’ retreating back with an extremely frustrated expression.

“Go, Haruto.” Aishia said.

“...Aishia?”

“You’re upset, no?”

Rio’s eyes widened at how Aishia had seen through him. “But...” Rio frowned as he looked at Celia. There was a great number of revenants. In a battlefield this chaotic, there was a chance Celia could be in danger too.

“No, Haruto,” Celia said in a cool voice.

“...Cecilia?” Rio’s eyes widened slightly.

“Remember what I said to you. You need to prioritize what you think is right — no, what your feelings tell you to do. Though we’re in opposite positions, it’s a similar situation to when you saved me, no? I don’t want you to make that face because of me. You look like you’re suffocating right now,” Celia said with a sad frown.

“...Okay.” Rio nodded with quite the guilty look. He wanted to act purely for his own sake right now, but he was feeling extremely reluctant about it, wondering if this was something that could be forgiven. However, he was the one who had said a similar thing when he pushed Celia out of the marriage she didn’t want.

“It’s my turn to save you this time. Well, I can’t do much compared to you, but... Terra Carcerem.” Celia suddenly crouched down and placed both her hands against the ground, chanting a spell. A magic circle immediately appeared on the surface, and the magic activated with practically no delay at all.

W-Wow! Who are they? They’re so cute! Both of them are too beautiful to be real! she thought to herself, surprised. However, she didn’t let it show on her face at all.

“I’ve been staying in this room with the two you see over there. The blonde-haired girl is Cecilia, while the peach-haired girl is Aishia,” Rio said.

“Nice to meet you, I’m Cecilia,” Celia greeted first with refinement. Aishia also gave a formal greeting and bowed once.

“I’m Aishia. Pleased to meet you.”

“...I’m Liselotte Cretia. It’s nice to meet you. The two of you are both very beautiful.” Liselotte returned the greetings in a slight daze, voicing her thoughts directly out loud.

“Why, thank you very much,” Celia said with a sociable smile.

The Professor sure is used to this, Rio thought in awe at Celia’s friendliness.

“Then, can the two of you wait in the room at the back? I have things to discuss with Lady Liselotte about last night.”

“Yup, we know.” Aishia nodded in agreement, heading for the back room.

Celia lowered her head respectfully before following Aishia. “Please excuse us.”

“Have a seat, please.” Rio offered Liselotte the head seat.

“...Yes, thank you. I’ll sit over here.” Normally, Liselotte would never hesitate before anyone no matter how highly ranked of a noble or wealthy of a merchant they were, but at this moment, she chose a lower seat with slight nervousness. She couldn’t sit in the head seat when she had come to apologize.

Rio noticed how Liselotte’s expression was rather stiff and spoke up as he remained standing. “Are you nervous, by any chance?”

Liselotte considered denying it for a moment, before agreeing. “No, umm... Perhaps.”

“Actually, I feel the same. I’ll prepare tea first, so please wait a moment.”

Contrary to his words, Rio smiled gently. He stepped away to the mini kitchen in the room and returned with a tray soon after. He placed the tray on the table and sat down opposite to Liselotte.

“It’ll take some time for it to steam, so let’s start our discussion first,” Rio suggested in a calm tone.

“Umm, I’m sorry. I’m here to apologize, yet I’ve troubled you with such inconveniences.” Liselotte frowned somewhat dejectedly.

“It’s no trouble at all. All I’ve done is welcome you with some tea.” Rio shook his head with a friendly smile. That was enough to show that he wasn’t in a bad mood.

“I am most grateful. Then, without delay, may I once more offer my most sincere apologies for the trouble that happened at my store last night?” Liselotte bowed her head in shame and finally broached the main issue at hand.

“I don’t believe you have anything to apologize for regarding that incident, Lady Liselotte...” Rio said with a frown. The dispute last night was simply bad luck, he thought. He had no complaints about how the inn had handled it. If anything, the inn employee had tried to protect Rio and his party proactively, and Aria’s investigation was handled politely, too.

“No — it’s the inn’s duty to ensure the customer has a comfortable time. An issue like that should have been stopped before it reached you, and for that we will reflect deeply on how we can do better,” Liselotte said apologetically.

“But the ones who caused it were nobles. While they may have come from another kingdom, the difference in social status still made it difficult to react. In that regard, I believe the staff last night reacted in the best way possible,” Rio offered carefully.

In a society with a class system, people were not equals. No matter how unfair it was, there were times when one had to endure. To upset those social ties and act however one pleased would be making an enemy of society itself.

“...What happened was disgraceful.” Liselotte bowed her head with a shamed expression. Since the matter did involve nobles, it was true that the incident last night was beyond their means. Even so, the inn’s handling should have been criticized — yet Rio didn’t do that. That made it sting even more.

“It is what it is... We have no complaints about the inn staff nor you, Lady Liselotte. If anything, I am more concerned with my relations with the other two involved. How should I treat them from now on?” Rio asked, changing the topic. No matter the official verdict of no fault being placed on Rio’s side, there was still the fear that those in power would hold a grudge against him.

“Duke Huguenot expressed his desire to apologize to you. He said the two who caused the commotion would receive their due punishments. He wished to convey his greatest sincerity.”

“...Is that so.” Rio nodded hesitantly. Nobles were known to be capable of acting the complete opposite of their words without batting an eye.

“If Duke Huguenot or the other two who caused the problem last night ever seek more trouble from you, I promise to stand on your side,” Liselotte said, reading Rio’s apprehensions.

“...Thank you very much. As for our side, in order to prove that this incident has been settled peacefully, it would be reassuring to receive a contract or documentation with compensation or a settlement.”

“I understand. Then, allow me to assist in the documentation as the mediator.” Liselotte immediately agreed.

He seems used to this, she thought in awe at Rio’s quick thinking. A contract would have the ability to deter recurrences. Experienced merchants would write one up whenever conflict arose, but writing contracts wasn’t a thought process that most commoners would have. If Rio hadn’t been the one to bring it up, Liselotte would have suggested it herself.

“Thank you very much.” Rio smiled, reaching for the tea set on the table. After moving the hot water used to warm up the cups into a different receptacle, he started to pour the tea with experienced hands.

“...You seem very familiar with this,” Liselotte commented in awe at Rio’s skill.

“One of my companions is very fond of tea, so we often drink it together.” Rio replied with a gentle smile.

“Is that so...” Liselotte uttered in an expression of interest. Meanwhile, Rio finished pouring the tea.

“Here you are. Be careful — it’s hot,” he said, offering it to Liselotte.

“Thank you. I’m looking forward to trying it,” Liselotte said with a smile and sipped at the tea elegantly. “Delicious,” she said with wide eyes.

The temperature, the time it was steamed, and the strength of the flavor was perfect. The tea leaves used were the highest quality Liselotte had hand-selected for the guest rooms, but the careful way each step was completed was what brought out the taste.

“It’s an honor to hear that.” Rio inclined his head as he took a sip of his own tea.

This is wonderful. On par with the tea Aria pours. Liselotte keenly savored the taste before letting out a small sigh of all her pent-up stress. These last few days had just been a series of one problem after another, accumulating quite a bit of mental exhaustion.

“I’m sure you must be very busy, so I shouldn’t keep you here for too long. Now that we’ve had a breather, shall we resume our previous discussion?”

“Yes. Then, in regards to the settlement contract, I shall first inform Duke Huguenot of the decision. Afterwards, I’ll prepare a meeting between you and Duke Huguenot, so that the details may be discussed.”

“I understand. I’m sorry to be a burden on you, but I thank you for your assistance.” Rio bowed his head deeply.

“I’m sorry for all the trouble that has been caused for you, too.”

“No, please don’t let it bother you.” Rio shook his head kindly at Liselotte, who had bowed her head in return.

“Much obliged. Also, if it is to your convenience, I’d like to invite you to lunch at my place today, as we promised earlier yesterday? Of course, your two companions are invited as well,” Liselotte said.

“...I apologize. Could the two in my company please be excused? They’re still a little tired and recovering from the shock of last night,” Rio requested, conveying his intention to attend alone.

“I understand. They must have gone through a lot already. Please extend my apologies to them as well. If there is a chance in the future, I shall apologize to them directly, too,” Liselotte agreed immediately, frowning in discomfort.

“Yes — I will pass the message on.”

◇　◇　◇

After that, Rio and Liselotte went to her estate. It was still morning, so they decided to work on drafting the contract before their meal.

Rio was first led into a waiting room, where he didn’t wait long before he was showed into a drawing room that Liselotte used on a daily basis. There, Duke Huguenot was waiting, opening his mouth to apologize to Rio before anything else.

Liselotte must have caught Duke Huguenot up to speed while Rio was in the waiting room, as they immediately began drafting the contract. There was a standard form for settlement contracts which they used as a base to discuss the details of accordingly.

Normally, when discussing the conditions of a settlement contract, the perpetrator and the victim would negotiate the facts and conditions which the settlement agreed upon. If an agreement could not be reached, it was common for the conflict to arise once more, but this time even Rio was surprised by how cooperative Duke Huguenot was. Duke Huguenot was meant to be present as Stewart and Alphonse’s representative, but he accepted all the facts and continuously suggested conditions that were favorable to Rio.

For example, he presented a compensation sum far beyond a typical case like theirs, an order preventing Stewart and Alphonse from harming Rio and his two companions in the future, and the penalty should that be broken...

Meanwhile, all Rio would be burdened with was not being able to not mention the actions of Stewart and Alphonse to third parties, with no particular penalties if he broke this condition. Rio hadn’t intended on spreading it anyway, so it wasn’t a very cumbersome burden.

And so, all the compromises were made on Duke Huguenot’s side. As a result, the contract draft was completed in a much shorter time than expected. Duke Huguenot took a breath and addressed Rio and Liselotte.

“I suppose this will do for now. Do the two of you have any other concerns?”

“I don’t have any particular objections at this moment in time, but something may come to mind later. I’d like to think about this for a few days before officially executing the contract. Would that suit you, Sir Haruto?” Liselotte said, looking at Rio.

“Yes, I do feel that it is a little one-sided in favor of me, but if you don’t have a problem with that...” Rio nodded in slight confusion.

“Of course it would be, seeing as none of the fault was yours,” Duke Huguenot said with a sociable smile. It was hard to believe he was the same man who once placed a false accusation on an innocent Rio’s head, and turned Latifa into an assassin.

“...Thank you for your consideration.” Despite finding the whole thing rather uncanny, Rio bowed his head respectfully.

“Then for the detailed wording and creation of the original contract, can that be left to you as a third party, Liselotte?” Duke Huguenot requested.

“Yes, leave it to me.” Liselotte nodded readily.

Duke Huguenot bowed his head at Liselotte, then turned to face Rio and apologized once more. “Sorry for the trouble. And Haruto, I apologize again for everything. My foolish son’s actions have caused you great pain, and for that I am sincerely regretful for.”

“No — if the matter is settled completely, then I have no more concerns about this issue.” Rio shook his head.

“...It pains me to admit, but I didn’t have much time with my son when he was younger, being occupied with my duties. Unfortunately, he grew up into an indulgent son. However, I swear as his parent to have him atone for his sins properly. In order to do so, I have one request to ask of you...” Duke Huguenot said, watching Rio’s expression.

“What is it?” Rio tilted his head rather warily.

“If you would so allow it, could you give them the opportunity to apologize in person? They have deeply reflected on their actions since then. It may be for their own egos, but they wish to apologize to you.” Duke Huguenot said with a strained smile.

“...Sure, I don’t mind.” Rio nodded hesitantly.

“Thank you. Then, Aria. Could you bring them here?” Duke Huguenot called out to Aria, who was waiting in the corner of the room silently.

“Understood.” Aria nodded, opened the door, and stepped outside.

“They’ve actually been ready in the room next door. It shouldn’t take long,” Duke Huguenot admitted. Sure enough, Aria returned not even a minute later, opening the door.

“Excuse me. Go ahead.” After opening the door, Aria invited Stewart and Alphonse inside. The two of them were giving off an extremely gloomy air.

“...Excuse me.” The two entered the room, greeting in rather dispirited voices.

They sure did a 180. Rio’s eyes widened at the sudden change in Stewart and Alphonse. It was hard to think of them as the same people who had been harassing girls and messing around in high spirits the night before.

“Come here.”

“Yes, sir...” As ordered, they approached Duke Huguenot.

“Good for you — Haruto here has agreed to give you the chance to apologize. Make sure you give a proper apology and express your gratitude for his generosity,” Duke Huguenot stated to Stewart and Alphonse in a calm and low voice. Stewart took the lead in kneeling down on the ground before Rio.

“...Please, accept my apologies. I am deeply repentant of last night, where I became drunk and let things get out of hand.” Stewart said his words of apology towards Rio.

“Please, accept my apologies.” Alphonse said shortly, kneeling on the floor with his forehead to the ground. His voice and body were both trembling. Just what emotion was running through him? For Rio, who knew them from his school days, it was an absolutely shocking scene to witness.

That being said, no matter how hard they had butted heads during their school days, Rio felt no satisfaction in watching them prostrate themselves forever. Rather, they were people Rio no longer cared about at all. It wasn’t even a matter of forgiving them or not.

“...It’s fine, please raise your heads.” Rio said in a rather blunt voice, accepting their apologies at once. Liselotte watched Rio’s face from the side as he did so.

After that display, Stewart and Alphonse immediately left the room. The remaining members exchanged pleasant talk until Natalie arrived and informed them that lunch had been prepared.

◇　◇　◇

Led by Aria and Natalie, Rio and the others entered the dining hall of the mansion. Inside the room was a long, rectangular dining table where Flora, Roanna, and Sakata Hiroaki were seated. There, Hiroaki was chatting away talkatively.

“Ah, Sir Haruto.” When Flora noticed them entering the room, she called out to Rio with a friendly smile.

...Me? Rio was taken aback by the fact that his name was the one called out, rather than Liselotte or Duke Huguenot with him, but he didn’t let it show on his face.

“It’s a pleasure to be in your presence once again, Princess Flora. Lady Roanna and Sir Hiroaki, too.” Rio placed his right hand over his chest and bowed his head respectfully.

“Yo, I heard about the mess you had to deal with,” Hiroaki said to Rio.

“Not at all, everything was resolved without any issues in particular,” Rio replied with a strained smile.

“Really. Well, sit down then,” Hiroaki invited Rio to sit as though it was his own house.

“Yes, please have a seat. Sir Haruto, Duke Huguenot,” Liselotte urged.

“Then I shall intrude on your table.” Duke Huguenot showed no sign of hesitation as he calmly lowered himself into a seat.

“This way, Sir Haruto.” Aria selected a seat for Rio and pulled it out quietly in invitation.

“...Then, excuse me.” Rio sat down nervously; Flora was seated right next to him.

“Umm, I know we’re all seated already, but is it okay for us to join you too?” Flora asked, peering up at Rio’s face beside her.

“I believe that, if anything, I should be the one asking if I may be here with everyone else?” Rio thought he’d be having lunch with only Liselotte and Duke Huguenot, so he was taken aback. Incidentally, Liselotte hadn’t known Flora and the others were inside the room until she entered herself, but had arranged for her attendants to prepare in advance either way, so she wasn’t particularly surprised.

“Eh, I’m sure it’s fine. This is a gathering of appreciation for you, after all. Having a meal with a hero and princess is a rare experience. Feel privileged, yeah?” Hiroaki huffed with a smug look.

Despite Rio being the main focus of the gathering, Hiroaki was acting like he was the master of the house. That being said, he was the hero on par with a servant of god, so it was endearing in a way.

“Yes, it’s an honor,” Rio agreed amicably.

“It isn’t meant to be a formal event, so please relax and enjoy yourself. The highest quality foods have been prepared for today,” Liselotte said somewhat apologetically. Even though she’d set up the event to show appreciation, Rio was being made to accommodate others even now.

Rio put on a sociable smile and thanked her cheerfully. “Thank you for your consideration.”

◇　◇　◇

Afterwards, Liselotte’s attendants carried the dishes in and the group promptly began their lunch party. Because it wasn’t a formal event, the meal wasn’t served in full-course style, but rather all brought out at once and laid out on the table like a feast. If anyone wanted a second serving of something they liked, they would ask the attendants to serve some for them.

The seating order was also informal. Hiroaki took up camp at the end seat, with Roanna seated beside him and Flora seated opposite. Beside Flora sat Rio, and next to Rio was Liselotte, whereas Duke Huguenot was seated opposite to Liselotte.

“The meat is top grade, as usual. I can tell it has been grilled properly as well. The chefs at Liselotte’s mansion sure know their stuff,” Hiroaki said with a satisfied expression, cheeks stuffed with steak.

“I am much obliged,” Liselotte said with a smile.

“But... eating good meat always makes me want rice too,” Hiroaki sighed quietly.

“I’ve actually used my connections with the Ricca Guild to prepare some rice...” Liselotte said, her expression somehow not looking too pleasant.

“What, really?” Hiroaki asked, showing a strong interest.

“Yes. You previously expressed your desire to eat rice, so I had some prepared exactly as the hero described. Aria—” Liselotte said, calling out to Aria, who was waiting in the room.

“Yes, my lady.” Aria nodded quietly, moving to stand before a small pot left on the waiter’s table. She served a small amount of rice onto a plate and carried it over to Hiroaki.

“This rice is supposed to be eaten as porridge, like threshed wheat. It’s only cultivated in certain parts of Strahl and not particularly favoured by royalty or nobility, so I’m sure it must be the first time some of you may be seeing it,” Liselotte said, addressing everyone seated at the table.

In Strahl, it was common for grains other than rice to be used for porridge, but porridge itself was looked down upon by the noble class as something for the lower classes to eat. It would normally be impolite to bring that ingredient to the dining table of royalty and nobility, but it was a different story if Hiroaki, the hero, desired it.

“So this is the rice that Sir Hiroaki often spoke of...” Flora looked at the plate before gazing at Hiroaki with curiosity.

There was rice in Strahl, too? Rio’s eyes widened at that fact.

“Haha, I see. Well, I guess I could give it a try.” Hiroaki picked up his fork and scooped some rice, staring at it with a grin on his face before carrying it to his mouth.

“...Is it to your liking?” Liselotte asked quietly.

“Ah, this is definitely rice. It’s rice, but not the rice I want.” Hiroaki shook his head in disappointment.

“So, it isn’t satisfactory after all,” Liselotte said with a wry smile, as though she expected that reaction.

“...What do you mean?” Flora asked curiously, cocking her head.

“It’s dry and the rice grains don’t stick to each other at all. To put it simply... it’s bad. It’s not the type of grain that should be cooked and eaten in this way to begin with. Though it probably tastes good if you make it into porridge and season it...” Hiroaki explained in Liselotte’s place.

“I agree. That’s why I had my chefs experiment and make something delicious to eat. Would you like to give their cooking a try?” Liselotte immediately suggested to Hiroaki.

Interest piqued, Hiroaki nodded heartily. “Oh? You sure are well prepared. As expected of you. Sure, bring it out.”

“Then, Aria. Please prepare enough for everyone.”

“Yes, my lady,” Aria agreed respectfully and began serving with the other attendant girls. Before long, two plates appeared before Rio. One had regular white rice, while the other one had the risotto.

“Everyone, please feel free to try and compare the differences between two types of cooked rice,” Liselotte stated cheerfully.

“What an interesting idea... I shall give it a try. Hmm...” Duke Huguenot said, starting with the white rice.

Meanwhile, Hiroaki had already eaten the risotto. “It’s great! It’s just like cheese risotto!” he said happily.

“Thank you. I see Sir Hiroaki knows about this dish, then. As you can see, it uses cheese. Did you say it was called risotto?” Liselotte asked curiously while smiling.

“Yeah, it’s the name of a similar food in my world. It was prepared in a different way compared to porridge, right?” Hiroaki nodded, confirming with a knowing look.

“Yes, it is as you discerned. The name of the food hasn’t been decided yet, so we will take this chance to name it after your risotto,” Liselotte said with a grin.

“Sure, I don’t mind.” Hiroaki nodded contently.

...This hero, does he not realize that Liselotte could have recreated this risotto using Earth knowledge? Rio doubted in his head. However, at present, he had no reason to interrupt and ask, and was content to observe quietly without overstepping.

Flora also took a bite of the risotto and offered her thoughts with a beaming smile. “This... risotto, was it? It’s very delicious.”

“Yes, I’m surprised.” It seemed like Roanna was also pleased with the taste. Duke Huguenot was also smacking his lips in awe.

“My compliments to the chef. To think a grain food could taste this good...”

“I am pleased to see it was to your liking.” Liselotte accepted their reactions happily, before turning to ask Rio who had just taken a bite of his risotto too. “What did you think, Sir Haruto?”

“It’s wonderful. I never imagined I’d be eating rice again,” Rio said with a smile. Liselotte looked at him, surprised.

“...Is it possible that you’ve eaten rice before, Sir Haruto?”

“Yes, actually. During my travels across various lands.” Rio disclosed just enough information that was within the truth. In actuality, he ate rice on a daily basis and often made risotto to eat, too, but decided against saying that out loud.

“Umm, how old were you when you started your journey, Sir Haruto?” Flora asked nervously, interested in Rio’s travels.

“...I was eleven years old.” Rio answered with the same number he gave Aria before, staggering the year he began his journey by one year. Rio had fled from the kingdom of Beltrum when he was in his sixth year of the Royal Academy, so he was actually twelve.

“Eleven...” Flora muttered quietly, seemingly frustrated.

Hiroaki narrowed his eyes at Flora’s expression. “Come to think of it, how old are you?” he asked Rio.

“I am sixteen.”

“Oh. So, the same age as Roanna... And one year older than Flora and Liselotte. But how did you travel from such a young age? In this world, you have to walk everywhere if you’re not a noble. Well... I guess it’s possible this has something to do with your parents?”

“No, both my parents died before I started my journey. I mostly traveled alone, but I did travel with others for part of the way.”

“Ah, I see. So your parents have passed already. Sorry for asking about that.” Even Hiroaki was able to sense the mood and scratched his head awkwardly.

“No, don’t let it bother you.” Rio shook his head with a smile.

However, Flora pushed further in questioning Rio. “Umm, then why did you choose to travel alone, Sir Haruto? Didn’t you have somewhere you were living before?”

At that, Liselotte, Roanna, and Duke Huguenot all widened their eyes in curiosity, finding it to be an assertive stance for Flora.

With a pensive look, Rio searched for the right words. “Actually, I was searching for a person connected to my deceased parents. My parents were nomads to begin with, so they barely had any acquaintances in the area, and weren’t very attached to the land, either.”

“...Then where did you live originally?” Flora asked further. Her posture had completely turned to face Rio beside her, staring at his face closely.

“Hey, now. Flora. Aren’t you prying into his past a little bit too much now?” Unable to continue to simply watch, Hiroaki admonished Flora.

Flora gasped as she came to her senses. “Ah, no... umm. That’s not what I intended... Please forgive me!” she apologized to Rio in a panic.

In order to avoid making Flora feel bad, Rio shook his head with a friendly smile. “No, don’t worry about it. If anything, I’m sorry for not having anything more interesting to say.”

“No, no — your story was of great interest to me. But setting the past aside, do you plan on ever settling somewhere eventually?” Duke Huguenot shifted the focus of the questions from Rio’s past to his future.

“That’s a good point. I’m still in the middle of my journey, so I’m not sure yet.” Rio dodged the question with a forced smile on his face.

“Hahaha. In that case, feel free to place the Kingdom of Beltrum in your sights as a place of permanent residency. With your sword skills, I’d hire you on good terms.” Duke Huguenot tried to scout Rio with determination, all while wearing a bright smile.

“Oh, my. If we’re talking about a swordsman of Sir Haruto’s level, I’d like to put my name out there, too.” Liselotte kept Duke Huguenot in check immediately.

“My my, it seems a rival has appeared already.”

“Fufu, but of course. I won’t let you get the lead right in front of my eyes.”

“Hahaha. We cannot remain in Amande forever, after all. We’re always in need of talented people, so being able to meet someone like this is a valuable opportunity. I must make the most of it,” Duke Huguenot said pleasantly, looking at Rio.

“...I am grateful for the offer. If fate ever leads me there, I will rely on you at that time,” Rio said, giving a diplomatic and safe reply.

“Hmm. Seriously speaking, we would be able to provide somewhere for you to use your sword skills as much as you want. And a career path upwards, too. Feel free to consider it as one of your options in life.” Duke Huguenot didn’t seem to have any intentions of allowing the conversation to end with lip service, appealing rather enthusiastically. However, he didn’t try to step forward too forcefully, wary of the trouble that Stewart and Alphonse had caused earlier.

“I will also be willing to welcome you at any time,” Liselotte reminded Rio casually.

“Wow, look who’s the talk of the town. Is this the birth of a new hero?” Hiroaki said, putting a damper on things.

“No, that would be out of the question. I would be no match for a real hero like you. The legend speaks of the ability to wipe out armies of monsters in a single blow, after all. If that were true, taking out a mere handful of minotaurs would be laughable in comparison,” Rio denied rather exaggeratedly, while also flattering Hiroaki for being a hero in the process.

“Ah, well. No matter how much effort you put in, real heroes have a status and power limited to only them. The wall that a fake could never surpass, or so they say. But if you’re aware of that, then maybe you might make it somewhere too.” Hiroaki smiled, now in a good mood.

“That’s very kind of you to say.” Rio bowed his head respectfully.

Meanwhile, Liselotte was watching Hiroaki with a worried face. “Oh, speaking of heroes. How much have you heard about the heroes being summoned all over the land, Sir Haruto?”

“Let me think... I’ve heard that the areas where pillars of light appeared were where the heroes were summoned. The rumors said that a hero appeared in the kingdom of Galarc too...” Rio took the opportunity to ask about the Galarc Kingdom hero. Finding more information about the Galarc Kingdom hero was one of his goals for getting close to Liselotte, so he was quite grateful for the topic at hand being brought up.

“The castle technically hasn’t released any information to the townspeople yet, but it’s hard to hide pillars that rose up so conspicuously,” Liselotte said with a strained smile.

“Ah, they said they would introduce her officially at the evening party, didn’t they? The female hero of Galarc.” Hiroaki said, sighing tiredly.

“An evening party... and a lady?” Rio asked hesitantly, stifling his overeager emotions.

“Yes, Lady Satsuki Sumeragi. That’s the name of the hero summoned in our kingdom.”

Sure enough, the woman was of the same name and gender as the person Rio was searching for.

“Lady Satsuki Sumeragi...” It couldn’t possibly be a coincidence. Rio was certain that the hero summoned in the Galarc Kingdom was Miharu’s upperclassman. Obtaining this information alone had made getting so close to Liselotte worth it.

“Actually, Sir Hiroaki is also set to attend that party. We also plan on unveiling him there,” Duke Huguenot said while looking at Hiroaki.

“Well, I’m not a big fan of being put on stage, but I guess this is another part of being a hero.” Contrary to his words, Hiroaki shrugged with a smile that didn’t seem all that displeased.

“...It sounds like quite the high-class event.” Rio said, eyes wide.

“Actually, there are rumors the hero summoned in the Kingdom of Centostella will also be in attendance. It’s not confirmed, though, and the hero’s name is also hidden still,” Duke Huguenot said.

“Oh my...” Rio uttered in interest.

Finally, a big leap in progress. I can tell Miharu and the others the good news too.

He sighed in relief at the situation finally taking a turn for the better.

“Wow... But he should pull back soon, don’t you think? He’s been fighting for a while, right? His magic essence won’t last,” Natalie said worriedly.

“Indeed. Now that we’re here, he can retreat and rest,” Cosette agreed immediately. “Sir Haruto!”

Rio retreated to the road with perfect timing.

“Erm, I believe you’re Cosette and...”

“This is Natalie. I’m honored you remember me.” Cosette smiled happily.

“I’m Natalie, one of Lady Liselotte’s attendants. It’s nice to meet you, Sir Haruto. Thank you for your assistance in these trying times.” Natalie bowed respectfully.

“I thank you on behalf of my master.” Cosette lowered her head at Rio with a truly adorable smile.

Rio gave a short shake of his head, looking around at the monsters in the square before getting right to the point. “Not a problem. I actually have a small request.” The monsters seemed to be wary of Rio, observing from a distance.

“What is it?” Natalie asked.

“I actually made my acquaintances wait back at the inn, so they haven’t evacuated yet. I’d like to go back and meet up with them,” Rio stated succinctly.

“Is that... so...” Natalie hesitated for a moment.

It would be a hindrance to have Rio leave, as the minotaur and the unidentified monsters were still lying in wait behind the goblins and orcs. If they all attacked at once, it would be extremely difficult to defend the area.

However, Rio wasn’t a soldier or adventurer of Amande to begin with — he was meant to be a commoner with no military duties. His assistance right now was completely voluntary, so Natalie couldn’t insist that he stayed to fight.

However, Rio seemed to sense Natalie’s apprehension. “In exchange for leaving this place to you, I’ll finish off that minotaur. How about it?” he suggested as a compromise. Unlike the west gate, only one minotaur had spawned at the east gate. On top of that, there were fewer revenants than the west gate. The threat would lessen greatly if he defeated the minotaur.

“...You are a commoner, so of course. We have no reason to hold you back. But the minotaur is at the rear.”

Natalie looked closely at the minotaur waiting outside the gate. Chronologically, it would have to be defeated last. While it could be attacked with long-distance magic, the minotaur’s physical abilities would probably allow it to evade the speed of an average attack.

“No, I’ll take care of it from here,” Rio declared firmly.

“...E-Excuse me?” Natalie inclined her head in confusion at how that would be possible.

“Then... here I go.”

Rio stepped into the fray again. A bright glow enveloped the blade of his sword as he stood poised with the tip pointed at the minotaur.

“Geehee?!” The monsters were glaring warily at Rio. Then, after communicating with a shared look, they all leapt at Rio at once. “Geeheehee!”

“?!” Natalie and the others gawked. A cannonball of magic essence coated in wind spirit arts had just burst from the tip of Rio’s sword. The single shot traveled past the wall at the speed of sound.

“Geehee?!” The monsters that had leapt at Rio were blown away by the aftershock, and the cannonball of essence wrapped in wind ripped through the minotaur’s heart with precision.

“M...rogh?! Mroh...?” Even the minotaur didn’t understand what had happened. It had no time to react, finding itself kneeling to the ground. It died, just like that, crumbling helplessly.

I’ll do one more push, just in case. With that thought, Rio poured essence into his sword again. A windstorm raged from his sword. Rio closed in on the monsters at the front and slammed the storm into the monsters.

“Buhee?!” Several dozens of orcs and goblins were blown away.

“...” Natalie and the others behind her were completely stunned.

“Now, I’ll excuse myself here.” Rio turned back and bowed once, as Natalie returned to her senses with a gasp

“Y-Yes! Thank you so much!”

“...Sir Haruto is wonderful,” Cosette said vacantly to Rio, who couldn’t help but be confused.

“Huh?”

Natalie shoved Cosette away in a panic. “Geez, what are you saying?! Sir Haruto, please don’t mind this one and be along your way. Take care!”

“...Yes. The same goes for everyone here.” Rio smiled in faint amusement before rushing off to the center city where the inn was.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, inside Liselotte’s mansion, Hiroaki, Flora, Roanna, and Duke Huguenot had evacuated to a guest living room. Inside stood four knights as guards, including Stewart Huguenot and the elite squad commander, Raymond Brandt.

Hiroaki’s leg shook nervously while he sat on the sofa. “Ah... Is it normal for monsters to attack cities this regularly?”

“While it isn’t a regular occurence, it isn’t unheard of, either. There have been cities and towns that have been annihilated by monsters in the past,” Duke Huguenot answered calmly.

“I see...” Hiroaki heaved a dramatic sigh.

He seems to be rather worked up. The fear from the previous fight must be taking an effect. Duke Huguenot narrowed his eyes. Normally, Hiroaki would be boasting to feign confidence.

“Hmph.” Stewart huffed through his nose disparagingly as he looked at Hiroaki. He must have noticed, as he stared back at Stewart.

Realizing his mistake, Stewart cleared his throat with exaggeration. “...Excuse me. My throat was dry from nerves.”

Duke Huguenot glared at Stewart, and he averted eyes from his father in a panic. A tense air hung over the room.

◇　◇　◇

Elsewhere, at the square just before Amande’s west gate, Aria aggressively lead her subordinate attendants, experienced soldiers, and adventurers against the crowded square of monsters.

“There’s just too many.”

No matter how many they defeated, the monsters kept coming in from outside the gate. There were simply too many. Aria grumbled as she calmly beheaded the orc before her.

There’s clearly more than when the monsters attacked in the forest. I’d love to clear them all up at once with large-scale magic, but I have to be careful not to run out of magic essence. Those things are waiting at the back, after all. She looked at the three minotaurs standing outside the gate.

“Guheehee.” The minotaurs were enjoying the view from afar with unpleasant grins.

But it’s baffling why they’re not invading into the city. Aria furrowed her brows in suspicion. Just like Rio, she had doubts towards the actions the minotaurs were taking. However, while Aria had the same thoughts, she couldn’t afford to move as freely as Rio. At least, not until she defeated the three minotaurs.

It’s a little risky, but I’ll have to move forward a bit more, Aria decided boldly.

“Captain Mattias,” she called out to a handsome male fighting nearby. He was in his late twenties and wearing higher quality combat clothes than the other soldiers, wielding a sword with a unique design in his hands. It was the enchanted sword Liselotte had temporarily lent him.

“What is it, Miss Aria?” The man named Mattias cut down an approaching monster easily before replying in a flirtatious tone unsuitable for a battlefield.

“It’s disconcerting how the minotaurs have showed no movement. Shall we leave this place to the others and head outside the gate to take care of them?”

“...Just you and me?” Mattias asked, seemingly taken aback.

“Yes,” Aria nodded solemnly.

“You serious?”

“This is not the time to be making jokes.”

“I figured. Well, if it’s an invitation from you, I guess so. Let’s do it. I wouldn’t want to exhaust myself here before facing those things last, anyway,” Mattias said breezily, shrugging his shoulders.

Aria was about to reply, when...

“Kshaaa!” The dark-skinned revenants that had been waiting outside the gate suddenly let out a screech.

“Shaah!” The other revenants followed, all screeching one after another.

Aria braced herself with her brow furrowed in suspicion. “...What’s going on?”

“MROOOOOH!” The minotaur let out a tremendous roar, loud enough to echo through all the areas of Amande.

“What? What is it?” Mattias asked in confusion.

“Kshaa!” The twenty or so revenants suddenly started running towards the gate all at once.

“What?!” Even Aria was taken aback by that. The revenants used their inherent physical abilities to rush inside the gate.

“Bring those down no matter what!” Aria ordered with determination. And yet...

“MROOH!”

Suddenly, the minotaurs moved too. With nimble movements unsuited for their giant size, they made a running leap over the gate and straight to the middle of the square.

Despite the panic on her face, Aria voiced her orders calmly. “Attendants, take out the revenants! Everyone else, continue to concentrate on the goblins and orcs! Captain Mattias!”

“Got it. Let’s do something about those big guys!” Mattias responded resolutely.

◇　◇　◇

At the same time, at the north ramparts of Amande, Lucius and Reiss were hiding in a back alleyway.

“That’s the signal. I couldn’t hear any voices from the east, so I guess they were taken out,” Reiss muttered quietly.

“It’s finally our turn. My body’s stiff to all hell now.” Lucius said, stretching lazily.

“Let us hurry. It appears the decoy monsters will be eliminated faster than expected. The real show begins with you. I’m counting on you, Alphonse.” Reiss urged for their departure, looking at the black revenant standing near them.

“Yeah. Leave it. To me,” Alphonse said, nodding with a grin of delight.

◇　◇　◇

At the same time, Rio was moving towards the inn he had stayed in before. The monsters’ attack had begun when the surroundings were still dark, but now, the sun was rising and everything was much brighter. Citizens were still evacuating through the square before the inn, but there were much fewer people than before. The large numbers of soldiers directing the evacuation were gone too; it seemed as though the evacuation had proceeded smoothly. Then, just as Rio landed in front of the inn while surveying the area, the roar of the minotaur at the west gate echoed through the city.

“MROOOOOH!”

...The voice of the minotaur at the west gate, Rio guessed correctly. The situation was changing by the moment, and it was possible that the roar just now was a sign of something worse to come

I’d better hurry. Rio thought, heading into the inn and towards his room with haste. But the door opened from the other side first, Aishia coming out to greet Rio.

“Welcome home.”

“I’m back, Aishia,” Rio replied with a smile; Celia poked her head out from behind Aishia.

“Welcome back!” she said with a gentle smile of relief.

“I’ve returned — sorry for making you wait so long.”

“No, that’s fine... But how is it outside? I saw Aria heading towards the west gate from the window, but what was that roar just now...?”

“The number of monsters at the east gate has fallen a lot, so it should be fine now. I believe the roar was a minotaur at the west gate, but if Aria’s there, then I think they’ll be well-matched.”

While Aria was could handle multiple minotaurs and revenants at an equal or higher level of combat to them, there were just too many monsters at the west gate. So he couldn’t say anything too optimistic.

“What do we do now?” Aishia asked.

“I’m thinking of going on to assisting the defense of the city and having Professor and Aishia evacuate to outside of the city.” Not wanting to cause unnecessary concern, Rio hid the strange feeling he had about the monsters and told them his next actions.

“Got it,” Aishia nodded immediately with no hesitation. Celia watched Rio’s expression and nodded anxiously.

“...Okay.”

“With the professor in a safe location, I’ll be able to fight to my heart’s content too. Can I ask this of you?” Rio addressed Celia with a troubled look. Having it put that way made it hard for Celia to refuse.

“...Okay.” Despite the worried look on her face, Celia still nodded obediently.

“Thank you. Please evacuate outside the south gate. It leads to open farmland, and there are no monsters there. I’ll accompany you partway — if the streets are empty, we can fly through the air part of the way.”

“Yup, got it.”

“Let’s get out of here.”

◇　◇　◇

And so, Rio and the girls left the inn.

There were even less people in the square out front than before, but evacuating residents could still be spotted here and there. They were hurrying along, cowering from the minotaur’s roar.

“We should go too. This way.” Rio checked the sight of the evacuees before the inn and took a step towards south in order to lead Celia and Aishia.

“Haruto, monster!” Aishia exclaimed with a gasp.

“Kshaaa!” The revenant’s screech echoed through the square.

“...Sorry. I was slow to realize,” Aishia apologized guiltily.

“No, it’s fine. Your detection of them is purely intuitive. Take the professor and fall back to the inn for now,” Rio said. Thankfully, the revenants surging into the square had yet to notice their presence. However, there were people they had spotted. Just in front of them was a mother and daughter, running away from a grey-colored revenant that had targeted them.

“Eek...!” They screamed, parent and child cowering in fear.

“Rrrgh...” The revenant glared at the two with a ferocious look.

The mother, around her thirties, collapsed as her knees gave out. “Ah...”

“N-No! Don’t come closer! Go away!” The girl was around ten years old and stood before her mother resolutely.

“Mireille, run away!” The mother called out to her daughter in a panic. An unpleasant possibility crossed the back of Rio’s head; he definitely didn’t want Celia to see this.

This is bad. Rio burst into a run on reflex.

Using wind spirit arts to push himself forward and accelerate, he moved at a tremendous speed to close the distance between them in an instant.

The revenant was sent flying by Rio’s punch. “Gufuh?!” It crashed to the ground with a loud noise and rolled.

“Kshaaa?!” The other revenants in the square noticed the commotion. There were others besides the mother and daughter that had been targeted by the revenants, but all the revenants now had their attention drawn to Rio. There was a total of four of them, including the one Rio had just sent flying.

“Over here!” Rio yelled to attract even more attention to himself, drawing his sword from the sheath at his waist.

“Shaah!” With that, the revenants all attacked Rio at once. Rio charged towards the closest approaching revenant and thrust his sword through its heart, ending it in one blow.

“?!” The other two froze in shock. Rio took that opportunity to close in on one of them, once more thrusting his sword through its heart with precision. Then, once he pulled his sword out, He turned back and landed a knee-kick into the abdomen of the other one approaching from behind.

“Vuh...!” The revenant easily lifted into the air. Rio kicked off the ground and pursued its body in an instant, finishing it off in a similar single blow by stabbing it through the heart. All that was left was the one Rio punched away first.

“Vurrgh...” Rio closed in on it instantly as it staggered back to its feet, and once again, stabbed it through the heart like the others to finish it off.

He withdrew his sword. “...Phew.” With the mental fatigue kicking in, he sighed quietly.

“...T-Thank you so much!” The mother that had been watching Rio’s fight in a daze snapped back to her senses after a pause and thanked him.

“...No, I’m just glad to see you aren’t hurt. Can you stand?” Rio asked, approaching the mother and offering his hand.

“Yes, I’ll manage...” The mother grabbed Rio’s hand and hesitantly stood up.

“T-Thank you so much, mister! Mom, are you all right?” Mireille asked, running over to support her mother.

“I’m fine,” the mother replied, giving an awkward smile to reassure her daughter.

“Mom? Mireille?!”

Chloe came running in her attendant uniform. She stopped in her tracks when she spotted Rio, before her expression changed at the sight of the mother and daughter. They appeared to be family.

Chloe’s mother. Hm? That means... she’s the innkeeper from back then, huh? Rio realized the mother was the one who had managed the inn he had stayed in several years ago. He also recalled there was a little sister, though he had forgotten her name.

“U-Umm, why are my mother and sister...?” Chloe asked Rio in confusion.

“We were being attacked by monsters when this man saved us! He was really strong!” Mireille explained proudly.

“R-Really? Thank you for saving them!”

“It was nothing... But why are you here, Chloe?” Rio asked. “U-Umm, because some of the humanoid monsters got into the city, so the others went to exterminate them while I was sent to report to Lady Liselotte,” Chloe answered with a troubled look. She seemed to be in a hurry, and her explanation was sparse. Just then, other citizens started gathering nearby.

“Ooh, Li’l Chloe!”

“Are ya hurt, Rebecca?”

“Thanks a lot, boy. You really saved us.”

Everything got noisier all at once.

“Ah, umm... S-Sorry. I’m in a bit of a hurry right now. Could everyone here quickly evacuate within the north walls? If you inform the soldiers at the ramparts, I’m sure they’ll let you in.” In her rush, Chloe gave only essential instructions.

“Oh, that’s right. Okay, you get outta here, Li’l Chloe! We’ll evacuate with this boy here,” A good-natured middle-aged man said, looking at Rio.

“No, umm...” Rio had no intention of heading to the north district, so he found himself at a loss for how to answer.

“Go send them off, Haruto.” Celia said, appearing with Aishia in tow. The two of them had cloaks on top of their clothes with hoods that hid their faces.

“Cecilia...” Rio looked at Celia and frowned worriedly.

“It’s okay — you don’t have to worry about me.” Celia said to Rio apologetically. The ramparts were right before them anyway; even if he were to go there, it wouldn’t take much time to reach the entrance.

“...I understand. I’ll get going, then.”

Rio steeled himself to head towards the gate of the north ramparts.

◇　◇　◇

Rio and the others arrived at the rampart gate within a matter of minutes. There were soldiers waiting before the gate, but like Chloe had said, they were allowed inside without incident.

“Phew, we can finally take a breather. Thanks again, mister.” Chloe’s little sister Mireille sighed in relief and thanked Rio once more.

“It wasn’t a big deal. All I did was walk with you.”

Honestly, all he had done was walk with them for the short distance between the square and the gate. No other revenants appeared along the way. From here onwards, it was the duty of the soldiers to protect them, so Rio’s job here was done.

“Excuse me. Firstly, thank you for escorting the citizens this far. If I may so ask, are you perhaps Sir Haruto?” One of the soldiers guarding the rampart interior asked Rio.

“...Yes, I am.” Rio nodded curiously, surprised his name and face was known by a stranger.

“So it was you after all. We were informed of your party’s appearance, so it was easy to spot you.”

“My party’s appearance?”

“Yes. The soldier took Rio aside and quietly explained things to him with a bashful glance at Celia and Aishia. “The truth is, Lady Liselotte has given us strict orders to escort you and your acquaintances to her mansion for shelter at the highest priority.” Celia and Aishia currently had their hoods lowered to speak with Mireille.

“Ah, I see.” Rio had an idea what the soldier was talking about; after all, Celia and Aishia certainly had an appearance that drew attention.

“I shall lead the way immediately, so please follow me. The mansion is the safest place right now, and both you and your acquaintances will be sheltered,” the soldier said with confidence.

Rio glanced at Celia. While he was conversing with the soldier, Mireille and the others were being led away by another soldier.

“Thank you for helping too, miss!” Mireille thanked Celia and Aishia politely before leaving.

Rio hesitated for a moment, but soon nodded his head. “...Then we shall take you up on your offer. Please lead the way.”

They had greatly swerved off course from his original plan to head outside the south gate, but it would be too unnatural to turn back now. Not to mention the possibility of encountering more revenants if they did. Taking refuge at the mansion was an acceptable alternative plan.

“Understood. Please, follow me.” The soldier bowed respectfully before taking the lead.

◇　◇　◇

A short time later...

Most of Liselotte’s personnel had relocated to the temporary command post in the garden, leaving the mansion essentially deserted. The only ones that remained in the mansion were those under heavy protection, like Hiroaki and the others.

“This way.” A dark black-skinned revenant walked along confidently inside the mansion. Lucius followed along behind it. Further behind him were four less dark-skinned revenants, walking in obedient silence.

“Sure makes things easier with a tour guide. Something impossible for the enhanced revenants.” Lucius bantered casually with no sense of tension at all.

“Hmph. The guest room. Is beyond the corner. Of that corridor,” Alphonse huffed somewhat unhappily.

“Gotcha. Right, so from here on it’ll be your time to shine. Leave the princess unharmed. You can smack the hero around too, as long as you don’t kill him,” Lucius informed Alphonse without any particular concern in his voice.

“Yeah. Leave it. To me. I’m stronger. Than any minotaur. Right now,” Alphonse replied with his disjointed words.

“Ah... Is that leftover intelligence you have left, or are you just broken? Well, whatever. Get going.” Lucius scratched his head before apathetically sending Alphonse away.

“Is someone there?” A voice echoed from down the corridor, having picked up on their conversation. It seemed to be the knights on guard in front of the room.

“Yeah, there is,” Lucius replied easily, showing no panic at all.

“Who’s there?” the voice asked dubiously from down the corridor.

“Oh no, it’s nothing. I’ve just got a little bit of business to tend to before making my way back. Don’t let it worry you.”

“...Wait. Step out of there.” The presumed knight ordered down the corridor in a stern voice.

“Good grief.” Lucius sighed in exasperation before walking forwards into the corridor. There were two knights standing on guard before the door to the room.

One of the knights approached Lucius and questioned him. “An adventurer? Are you alone? You were talking to someone, no?”

“Nah no one else. Feel free to go see for yourself.” Lucius assumed a cooperative attitude, standing to the side to make way and shrugging his shoulders.

◇　◇　◇

Less than a minute later, thunk went the sound of something hitting against the door of the room Hiroaki and the others were waiting in.

“...Hey, did you hear something against the door just now?” Hiroaki asked, staring at the door as he asked the others around him.

“Indeed I did,” Duke Huguenot nodded, sending an order to the knights with a look.

“Yes, sir.” There were four knights including Stewart guarding the inside of the room. One of them slowly moved to the door and opened it with a creak.

“Hey, what happened?!”

A pitch black fist came flying through the doorway. The knight was struck squarely in the face and sent flying towards the back of the room. Hitting several pieces of furniture along the way, he came to a stop with a loud crash.

“Kyaa?!” Flora, who had been sitting nearby, couldn’t help but scream.

“W-What’s going on?!” Roanna looked at the door in shock. “Ha. Ha. Ha.” The dark black-skinned revenant, Alphonse stood there and grinned eerily. Behind him were four paler black-skinned revenants.

“M-Monsters?! How could they be here?!” The other three knights — including Stewart — drew their swords reflexively.

“Go,” Alphonse ordered shortly.

“Vaah!” His subordinate revenants screeched and charged into the room. “Augendae Corporis!” The knights chanted at the same time, but the one to two seconds it took for the magic to activate were fatal. The revenants closed the gap and attacked the knights before they could finish enchanting their physical abilities.

“Shit!” The knights had no choice but to cancel their magic and swing their swords... but unfortunately, there was no way they could hurt the revenants without enhancing their physical abilities.

“They’re rock hard?!” Steel-like skin deflected the blades of their swords.

“Graagh!” The grey revenants went up one on one against the knights, grinning in delight. There were three knights and four grey revenants, which left one grey revenant and Alphonse free.

“Hey, what is the security doing?!” Hiroaki suddenly shouted at the corridor, but no one came running to save them.

“Hmph. Go.” Alphonse snorted in contempt, giving the order to the remaining revenant. It started running gleefully, charging into the back of the room to harass Hiroaki’s group.

“Shit! Head for the door! Run!” Realizing they would be cornered rats at this rate, Hiroaki ordered Flora and the others beside him before running for the door in a panic. He wasn’t just a hero for show, as his movements were clearly inhuman in speed.

“Eh, ah...” Unable to react on the spur of the moment, Flora was confused, but Roanna suddenly grabbed her by the arm.

“Princess Flora, this way!” Roanna said and ran after Hiroaki’s lead.

Thankfully, the knights were somehow managing to push back the revenants one by one. The room was spacious, leaving plenty of room for them to run between the gaps of the fights taking place.

On top of that, the leftover revenant that charged into the back of the room was just cackling to itself in delight, showing no signs of attacking them.

And so, as long as they managed to do something about the pitch black revenant camping before the only doorway in or out, they’d be able to get out. Duke Huguenot seemed to be thinking the same, following after Hiroaki behind Roanna and the others.

Their only hope was Hiroaki and his secret hero combat abilities. He had technically been on par or above with the knights in their sparring matches before. While he was fairly agitated at the moment, unlike the previous battle, he was heading for the monsters himself this time. It seemed like he wouldn’t be useless from fear this time.

“Move it! Come, Yamata no Orochi!” Hiroaki summoned his prided divine arms to his hand. With the beautiful blade in his grasp, he swung the sword at Alphonse, but Alphonse saw through Hiroaki’s movement easily and slipped right up close to him.

“Hmph.” Alphonse snorted, punching Hiroaki’s face with all his might.

“Gwoah?!” Hiroaki was easily blown to the back of the room.

“I’ve always. Wanted. To beat. This guy’s face in.” Alphonse cackled with satisfied laughter.

I-It talked?! W-What is this?! What in the world is that?! It’s so creepy! Roanna felt an instinctive sense of revulsion from the bottom of her heart at the fact the pitch black monster before her had spoken. Goosebumps crawled across her skin. The half-human-like shape of its body made it creepy already, but when it spoke human words, it was absolutely revolting.

“P-Princess Flora, get behind me...” Roanna said. She believed it was her role as a noble to become the shield for royalty. Meanwhile, Duke Huguenot was recoiling in a bad state.

“Kuh...” The knights were still fighting with the three revenants and unable to use their magic to enhance their abilities, so they were suffering quite a bit. Their breakthrough plan with Hiroaki had been flipped so easily, and there was nowhere left to run.

“You’re next. I won’t. Let you off. Easy. Understand?” Alphonse looked at Duke Huguenot intently, mouth twisting in a sinister grin.

“...What?” Duke Huguenot looked dubious. The capability to communicate meant there was a chance of mutual understanding. He suddenly wondered if they could obtain some kind of information.

“Ahaha!” But there was no time to think about that. In a single bound, Alphonse leapt upon Duke Huguenot and pummeled his fist with just the right about of power held back into Duke Huguenot’s abdomen.

“Guh. Gah... kgh...” Duke Huguenot collapsed to the floor, unable to stand the attack.

“F-Father!” Stewart’s expression changed when he realized Duke Huguenot was being attacked. He frantically swung his sword, trying to brush off the revenant he was facing. Meanwhile, Alphonse grabbed Duke Huguenot by the collar and lifted him easily off the ground.

“There’s still. More. Where that. Came from!”

“Hah, kknhh...” Duke Huguenot struggled to breathe, writhing in agony.

“Father! Move, you monster!” Stewart swung his sword desperately, moving the revenant in front of him out of his way. It let out a sinister cackle with a twisted grin.

“...No, Father! Release me!” Stewart attacked Alphonse desperately. Alphonse lightly evaded Stewart’s attack before tossing Duke Huguenot to the side roughly.

“Hee! Heehee! Oh, I know. I know.” With a pleasant smile, Alphonse turned back to Stewart.

“Shit! Die, die!”

“That. Won’t work.” Stewart swung his sword intently, but Alphonse’s inherently tough skin made his sword bounce off without a scratch.

“...Princess Flora, you at least must escape.” Roanna slowly inched towards the door, whispering to Flora quietly.

“Eh, ah... but you... but what about everyone?!” Flora’s expression changed with a gasp, showing deep disapproval.

“The physical abilities of that monster are abnormal. It’s amusing itself right now for some reason, but we’ll all be wiped out at this rate. Even if we tried to run, there’s a high possibility we’d be caught before we can use any magic. So at the very least, let us become decoys for you to get away,” Roanna said, giving a hurried but organized attempt at persuasion.

“N-No, I can’t! I can’t... that’s too...”

“Please, I beg you. If you let this chance go...” Roanna looked at Stewart in a panic.

“You monster! Monster!” Stewart had become desperate, slashing away at Alphonse, but it was clear that Alphonse was toying with him.

“Gahah. Gahahaha!” Alphonse laughed loudly, mocking Stewart. The same went for the revenants dealing with the other knights. Alphonse must have inspired them, as they were similarly laughing as they dealt with the knights.

“Damn it!” The knights facing them were pale and breathing heavily — they wouldn’t last long in this situation.

This was the only moment Flora could get away.

“Princess Flora! Princess Flora!” A voice calling for Flora could be heard down the corridor.

“Oh! Princess Flora is safe! Please help her escape!” Roanna suddenly thrust Flora towards the open doorway with all her might. Then she stood in front of the door to block it from any pursuing revenants.

“Kshaah!” The revenant at the back of the room started running towards Roanna.

“Roanna!” Flora called Roanna’s name in a panic, still in her state on the floor. Then, a man appeared from outside the room, grabbing Flora’s hand and easily pulling her into standing.

“Princess Flora, this way.”

“L-Let go of me!”

“I cannot do that. You must come this way.”

Flora objected heavily, but the man led her away from the scene without listening to her protests.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, Roanna used offensive magic to push back the revenants in the room.

“Photon Projectilis.”

A magic circle appeared at her hands, firing high-speed bullets of magic energy from its center. Roanna’s aim was precise and landed directly on the revenants that approached her from deeper in the room.

“Guh?!” The revenants that were hit in the body by the bullets staggered.

“There’s still more where that came from!” Roanna shot her bullets at the revenants facing the other knights. One shot, two shots, three — the bullets pummeled them mercilessly.

“Ah. Was I. Hit?” While Alphonse felt the impact, he brushed it off with a tilt of his head.

“?!” But Roanna didn’t falter; she continued hitting the revenants with her photon bullets.

“Argh!” An annoyed voice laced in furious anger echoed through the room. Roanna flinched and unthinkingly cancelled the magic she had activated.

“Ah?” The revenants attention was drawn in the direction of the angry voice. Duke Huguenot was collapsed on the floor, and the knights were exhausted. Which left —

“Yeah, I’m mad. I’m really mad now. Getting punched by those filthy hands of yours... Disgusting.” Standing there was Sakata Hiroaki.

“...You’re. Surprisingly tough. I hit you. With my full. Power.” Alphonse narrowed his eyes, impressed.

“Die, you cockroach!” Hiroaki yelled, attacking the unoccupied revenant nearby. The revenant promptly assumed a guard stance with both its arms raised, but —

“Guh?!” Its body was cleanly divided into two with a bam.

“This is total shit. Just die already,” Hiroaki said, moving to slash at the next nearby revenant in succession. His speed surpassed that of the paler black-skinned revenant, allowing him to exterminate the second one just as easily.

“Ugh, now I’m pissed off!” Hiroaki’s anger showed no signs of waning. He glared at the revenants with eyes full of loathing.

“S-Sir Hiroaki?!” Roanna’s eyes widened at the sudden change in the young man.

“Move, Roanna! I’ll kill them all!” Hiroaki yelled, charging towards Alphonse. Roanna couldn’t stand it and escaped to the side of the room.

“Grarh!” The remaining revenants attacked Hiroaki from both sides.

“Shut up!” Hiroaki swung his sword with a ridiculous stance, cutting down the revenants in a single swing. His blade was exceptionally sharp.

“What?!” Alphonse’s eyes widened in astonishment.

“You’re next, bastard! Die!” Hiroaki charged at Alphonse — the final one remaining — and gave a great swing of his sword from afar. Then, an abnormal amount of water came jetting out of the blade.

“Guh?!” Alphonse stepped back reflexively, twisting his body to evade the attack as he retreated into the corridor. Immediately, a torrent of water shot through the air. The blast of water pierced straight through the mansion wall, flying outside.

“Y-You!” Despite Alphonse’s enraged fury, he continued retreating into the corridor.

“Hold it!” Hiroaki promptly pursued him into the corridor, leaving Roanna and the other wounded men in the room. Once Hiroaki jumped out into the corridor, his eyes locked on Alphonse in the narrower space. He moved to launch another straight attack, but —

“Goodness,” a flat voice said.

“Ah?!” Hiroaki turned back toward the voice and instantly received a strong blow to the neck. His head was rocked violently, making him black out in no time at all. He fell to the floor heavily.

“Y-You’re...” Alphonse’s eyes widened in shock. Standing before him was Reiss. Sharp eyes looked down at Hiroaki from underneath his robe.

“...You, outside. Your role here is over. Go with the other revenants and buy time for Lucius to flee from here,” Reiss ordered Alphonse coolly.

“What? But...” Alphonse made to argue back.

“Just go already,” Reiss said in a hollow voice, interrupting any rebuttal.

“A-All right.”

“Good. There should be interesting prey for you outside as well. Now, I must hurry,” Reiss stated, departing from the scene promptly. Meanwhile, Alphonse headed outside the walls through the hole Hiroaki had opened up. Then, one beat later, Roanna nervously stuck her head out of the room.

“...S-Sir Hiroaki!” Upon noticing Hiroaki collapsed on the corridor floor, she hurriedly ran to him. However, once she saw he was breathing, she realized he was simply knocked out and sighed in relief.

Meanwhile, Reiss was lurking around the corner of the corridor.

Perhaps it was a mistake to call Lucius after all. While his abilities are exceptional, his ephemeral hedonism shows on his face as soon as he gets excited. He is more beast than man, really. The plan looks like it will work out, but at the cost of some needless headaches, Reiss thought as he quietly watched Roanna’s face.

That Alphonse too... The way he immediately ran to play in his excitement shows how far he is from the perfect specimen. Well, the base human was an imperfect creature to begin with, Reiss lamented.

“Well, he will be disposed of here. At least I’ll be able to measure the strength of the humanoid spirit and contractor before I leave,” he muttered before departing.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, a bit earlier, Flora’s hand was being pulled along by an unknown man.

“Umm, please, please let go of me! Where are you going?! We have — We have to call for help!” Flora protested at the man forcefully tugging her along while looking at the room behind her with Roanna and the others. The man was wearing a hood, hiding even his profile.

“Nah, that little lady’s already done for. She’ll be ruthlessly torn to pieces any moment now. If they weren’t playing around, it would’ve been over in ten seconds or so.” The man walking before her cackled in delight.

“Y-You... Who are you?” Flora asked fearfully. At a glance, he looked like an adventurer dispatched to protect the mansion, but something was clearly wrong. She wondered if he was taking advantage of the commotion.

The man suddenly came to a stop. “Nah, I’m not someone worth naming myself. But I suppose it’d be rude not to say in this position, so... Well, I’m human trash.” He faced Flora and temporarily removed his hood to answer with a grin, and Flora finally saw the man’s face clearly.

It was Lucius.

“U-Umm...” Flora stumbled for words.

“Ah, it was so funny earlier, I couldn’t help but watch for a bit. The good old fashioned servant-master relationship of royalty and nobility is so beautiful to see. What a wonderful scene that was indeed. I almost wanted to ruin it.” Lucius chatted away in a somewhat worked up state.

Flora was overcome with an indescribable fear and yelled in a panic. “S-Someone! Is anyone there?!”

“Hahaha, so you want to call for help? Well, be my guest.” Lucius smiled pleasantly, speaking to Flora.

“Y-You... What are you...?” Flora asked, clueless as to what Lucius’ aim was. Lucius had taken on a completely defiant attitude, making him seem so unnerving.

“Well, I’m here to kidnap you, actually. Though if I’m being honest, it doesn’t matter how I accomplish that, so I think I’ll have some of my own fun,” Lucius said indifferently.

“...I-I am your target? And you are using this chaotic situation to kidnap me?” Flora asked with a trembling voice.

“Well, to put it simply... yes. But bringing you back so easily like this is a little too boring. I’m going through all this trouble already, so I’m thinking of leaving my mark on you,” Lucius answered smoothly, grin on his face. Flora fell silent in question.

“For example, the little lady who entrusted you to me. What kind of face do you think she’ll make when she finds out she made the wrong judgement? Just imagining it thrills me,” Lucius said in an extremely flippant tone.

“...” For the first time in her life, Flora felt an indescribable sense of revulsion at the excessive wickedness in his words.

“Hahaha. For now, just seeing that expression of yours is enough. And didn’t I tell you earlier? The little lady’s done for already.” Lucius’ mouth twisted in a grin as reality sunk into Flora with despair.

“Ah — L-Let go of me, let go of me please!” Flora startled in alarm, trying once again to release herself from Lucius’ hold.

“Yet again, you...” Reiss appeared, addressing to Lucius from behind.

“Hey,” Lucius replied casually.

“Stop dawdling here and move already. The humanoid spirit has already come to the mansion. It would be bad to face that head to head,” Reiss said, sighing tiredly.

“Oh...?” Lucius’ eyes widened in interest.

“Just so you know...” Reiss started saying.

“I know, I know. I’ll head to the rendezvous point after this, so don’t worry. Just let me choose my own route, yeah?” Lucius said vaguely.

“Go, then,” Reiss sighed once more, urging Lucius away.

“You heard the man, princess. Come along now. Don’t put up a fight unless you want those beautiful legs to become severed.” Lucius put his hood on once more, then picked up Flora and threw her over his shoulder without letting in a word of protest.

“Eek — Kya?!” Flora screamed, but was bluntly ignored.

“Up we go.”

Lucius proceeded to run down the corridor, disappearing somewhere. Moments later, Hiroaki’s rage caused a cannon of water to blow a hole in the wall.

“Aah...!” The tremendous heat wave washed over Flora, making her let out a little scream and turn her face away, unable to bear the heat.

“...Hah, you’re one nasty bastard.” Lucius glared at Rio with hatred.

“Not as much as you. Let’s finish this soon,” Rio said, closing in on him.

“Sure you don’t need to capture me alive?” Lucius asked in desperation. “Unfortunately, I received no such orders.” Rio shook his head without hesitation before accelerating, swinging his sword with the full intention to behead the heavily battered Lucius.

“...Guh!” Lucius wrung out the last of his strength to avoid the slicing attack. However, Rio had seen through the fact Lucius still had energy left and thrust his knee straight into Lucius’ face.

“Gah! Aaah!”

His knee struck right where Lucius’ left eye was; Rio had felt a certain resistance. Lucius rolled across the floor, yelling uncouthly as he felt the greatest pain he’d been in since this battle began.

He must have his physical body enhanced, because he really is unyielding. In order to end him for sure, I must... Rio pointed the tip of his sword right at where Lucius’ heart was, but Lucius shifted his body by the slightest amount, avoiding the direct stab to his heart. However, the sword pierced through his upper body.

He was practically at death’s door.

“Guh... hah...” Blood was pouring out of Lucius’ mouth.

“Stubborn ass. I’ll just have to wipe any trace of you from this world,” Rio said, pouring magic essence into his sword. An intense heat radiated from his sword, melting Lucius’ flesh.

“Guh...! Aaah!!” Lucius yelled, unable to endure the pain. The light of Rio’s blade grew stronger, expanding its area of effect to melt the rest of Lucius’ body.

“But you still... need to... protect the princess, right...?!” Lucius yelled, using the final dregs of his power. Holding the pitch black sword in his right hand, a small amount of darkness flowed out of the tip.

“No!” Rio reflexively withdrew his sword and moved to Flora in an instant, embracing her before leaping into the air.

“Kya?!” Flora gave a small scream. The place she had been standing a short moment ago was covered in darkness, from which the tip of Lucius’ sword could be seen sticking out. If Rio hadn’t saved her, Flora would have been pierced through.

“Hah, hah... hah...” Lucius endured the pain to give a wicked grin. He had lost his left arm, endured his left eye being crushed, and had large holes all throughout his body. Though he had enhanced his physical body, his wounds were so serious it was a wonder that he was still alive.

“Uhm... Ah.” Flora realized that Rio had saved her and shuddered, shaking her body. She moved her hand in fear and flattened herself against Rio clingingly.

He’s hanging on by a thread. Still holding Flora there, Rio slashed his sword down vertically. A slicing wind laced with essence immediately flew out of Rio’s sword, closing in on Lucius crawling about the ground. However, the wind slash passed through where Lucius was lying and dispersed into the forest behind him, cutting down several trees along the way.

Lucius had changed locations at some point. “You’re late, damn it...” He raised his head and muttered resentfully upon spotting the figure through the blurry vision of his right eye.

“What a mess this is. If only you didn’t have that bizarre desire to play.” Standing there was Reiss. Clad in his cloak with the hood covering his face, he held the severely wounded Lucius in his arms.

“...I have business with that man.” Rio lowered Flora on the ground and addressed Reiss in a sharp voice.

“Unfortunately, I have business with him too.”

“I was here first.”

“No, no, no. You want to kill him, right? That means I won’t be able to finish my business, no?” Reiss stated nonchalantly.

“Then what will you do? Run away? Lucius, what about you? You going to run with your tail between your legs?” Rio taunted.

“...Hey, Reiss... Let go! I have... to kill him!” Enraged, Lucius spat out blood.

“Reiss?” Rio heard the name clearly.

“...That’s something I cannot do. The moment you undo your physical body enchantment, you’ll die. Even if you keep up the enchantment, your body will only last a few more minutes. There is no other choice but to withdraw here.” Reiss sighed as he spoke to Lucius, when a large number of light spheres floated in the air around them.

“Did you think I would let you run?” Rio poured a large amount of magic essence into his sword and called out to Reiss himself.

“Well, I do have some confidence in running and hiding my presence, after all. But who knows, against an opponent like you. There’s no telling until I try...” Despite the casual tone of voice Reiss took on, he observed Rio cautiously with a sharp look from under his hood. The blade of Rio’s sword was glowing with a dazzling light.

“...Here I go,” Reiss informed him with a chuckle. At the same time, Rio released a single blow to eliminate both men.

Haruto, above you! Suddenly, Aishia’s voice echoed in Rio’s head.

Rio turned his attention above him. “?!”

A pitch black flash was falling down to where Rio and Flora stood. Rio promptly changed the direction his sword was aiming from Reiss to the flash in the sky above.

“Guh?!” A tremendous shockwave blew all over the area. It was the clash of the attack Rio had released and the falling flash of light.

“Ah! Aah...?!” Flora watched the spectacle in shock from behind Rio.

“Hide behind me!” Rio ordered Flora in a frightening tone, and Flora moved behind Rio’s back in a panic. A few seconds passed like an eternity.

“Haaah!” Rio pushed back the black flash of light. A dazzling ray of light tore through the sky. However...

They’re gone. At some point, Reiss had disappeared carrying Lucius. He looked around, but there was no sign of their presences. Even if he tried to search for traces of magic essence with spirit arts, the fight until now had scattered essence all over the place. He had no choice but to give up.

Rio looked up at the sky with a sharp glint in his eye. There, flying far in the skies to the west, he spotted a black dragon-like creature and immediately guessed that the attack just now had come from that.

Did that man call it here? When he considered why it attacked in such a convenient way for Reiss and Lucius, he couldn’t help but feel suspicious. However, something like that hardly mattered to him right now.

They got away... Shit.

Rio grit his teeth with a shamed expression. With a wound that deep, there was a high chance he wouldn’t survive. He had what would have normally been a fatal wound, and even if he survived, his body was damaged too much to ever fight again.

But it was unacceptable. That man would probably survive. Rio had no evidence, but he couldn’t help but feel like that man would survive.

I’ll kill him. I’ll definitely find Lucius and kill him. As for Reiss... Rio felt a strong, bitter regret before he carved the name of the person who could hold a clue into his mind.

“U-Umm...” Flora called out nervously from behind Rio.

“...” Rio silently turned back.

Despite being the one to call out, Flora didn’t know what to say, moving her mouth without saying whatever she was trying to say.

“U-Umm... Sir R-Rio...” She grabbed onto Rio’s sleeve imploringly, whispering his name.

“Yes.” Rio nodded with a guilty look without averting his gaze from Flora.

Rio... That’s right. I’m Rio. He reconfirmed who he was in his mind. Starting today and from tomorrow onwards, Rio would live as Rio. Nothing from this experience would change that. Rio couldn’t become anyone other than Rio.

He would continue to live the path of Rio from tomorrow onward, despite the fact that it was a long, fruitless path in a battle with not his future, but his past.

However, a light shone on that gloomy road for him today, because he’d discovered that Lucius was alive. There was no need for pessimism. The empty road with no end he had been traveling on until now finally had a destination. There was no mistaking the path he had chosen. All that was left was to continue forward.

Rio slowly looked up at the sky and watched the bright dawn sunlight lead to tomorrow.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, far from Amande, in the underground of the Proxia Empire castle...

“Hnnghahh...” Lucius rolled on the floor as he spewed a large volume of blood from his mouth. But it wasn’t just coming from his mouth — blood was also pouring from the area where his left arm was amputated. Furthermore, he had a large hole in his abdomen, which consequently covered his whole body in blood.

Reiss looked down at Lucius with cold eyes. “Left eyeball ruptured, flesh gouged from abdomen to chest, left arm lost completely. In addition to the complex bone fractures throughout the whole body, the damage to your body is a little too severe. There’s no other choice.” He took out a giant gem from his chest pocket, its color a blood crimson.

“The incident this time should be a good lesson for you. I can’t have you dying on me, after all. Allow me to save you,” Reiss said, pushing the gem into the missing section of Lucius’ abdomen. Immediately, the gem melted away with an oozing sound, being absorbed by Lucius’ abdomen.

“Grah! F-Fuck! If — If I... had... my left arm... I could... have won!” Despite his face distorting with pain, Lucius bluffed insistently.

“...You’d have regained the strength to speak as soon as the healing process began. However, I doubt the result would have been any different even if you had your left arm. Give up. There is no way for you to win against him right now,” Reiss stated firmly, his face extremely exasperated.

“Guh...!” Humiliation and rage mixed in Lucius’ expression.

“But I have things to reflect upon myself this time. It seems I underestimated his abilities a little too much. Honestly, I’m at a loss for what to do. We can only accept our defeat quietly this time. In the future, we’ll have to put a hold on facing him alone. It would be best to avoid interfering,” Reiss said.

“W-What?!” Lucius’ expression was completely against it.

However, Reiss didn’t lend an ear to Lucius’ complaints. “I won’t let you object. You were the weak one this time, after all.”

Interlude: Let’s Make Uniforms!

Meanwhile, far, far away in the village of the spirit folk...

It was the middle of the day. Latifa and Sendo Aki were accompanied by their silver werewolf friend, Vera, as they returned to the house they were living together in. There, they found a group of four older girls gathered in the living room — Miharu, Sara, Orphia, and Alma.

“We’re home!” Latifa and Aki called out enthusiastically as they returned.

“Welcome home,” the older girls all replied to them warmly.

“Huh?! What are you wearing, Orphia?!” Latifa spotted Orphia’s figure and beamed from ear to ear.

“Fufu, the clothes from where Miharu lived before she came here,” Orphia replied, turning on the spot to show off her entire body. She had a beige blazer, a red ribbon at her chest, a knitted sweater, a plaid skirt, and black knee high stockings on. Orphia was wearing Miharu’s high school uniform from Japan.

“Uwah...” Latifa’s eyes were sparkling with awe.

Vera gazed at Orphia’s outfit curiously for a moment, before brightening up with a friendly smile. “Wow, you wouldn’t see those clothes anywhere in the village. But it’s really cute!” Beside her, Aki was also enchanted by the sight of Orphia in a school uniform. After a pause, she offered her opinion with a beaming smile.

“Yeah, the uniform really suits you, Orphia!”

“Ehehe, thank you.” Orphia thanked her with a smile.

“...Uni... form?” Vera tilted her head.

“The clothes that Orphia’s wearing. In the country we were from, older kids would go to school wearing the same clothes,” Aki immediately explained to Vera.

“That’s nice! Hey, I want to try it too. Can I please wear it, Miharu?” The fox tail Latifa was so proud of swayed from side to side as she pleaded at Miharu.

“Yes, of course.” Miharu giggled and agreed readily.

“Hmm... But I think that size may be a little too big for Latifa?” Sara stared at Latifa’s body and commented her doubts.

“Fufu. It was loose-fitting around Sara’s chest too, after all.” Alma said with a grin.

“It was perfect height-wise! Unlike you, Alma!” Sara objected in embarrassment, but Alma brushed it off nonchalantly.

“I am a dwarf, so I know I will be lacking in size in certain areas.”

“Geez!” Sara pouted cutely. Miharu giggled in amusement at the exchange between the two of them.

“Ah, then how about I lend you my uniform instead, Latifa?” Aki suggested.

“Huh? You have a uniform too, Aki?” Latifa’s expression brightened at once.

“Yup. I put it away in my room, so you can change there. Let’s go,” Aki said.

“I’ll wait here in anticipation!” Vera remained in the living room with the older girls. Not long after, Latifa and Aki returned, and Latifa was wearing Aki’s school uniform.

“...Ehehe, what do you think?” she asked with a smile, showing off her figure to the girls in the room. Aki’s uniform had a different design from Miharu’s, but it was also very cute.

Vera’s eyes sparkled, and she was the first to speak up. “Wah! It suits you so well, Latifa!”

“Ehehe, thank you,” Latifa said happily. She was still a primary school student when she lived in Japan as Endo Suzune, so she may have admired the school uniforms of middle school and high school students.

“Yes, you look great in it. Make sure you show Haruto too,” Miharu said to Latifa with a smile.

Latifa nodded happily. “Yup! But I’d want Onii-chan to see all of us in uniforms together, if possible. We should make them, just like we did with the swimsuits!”

“Huh? These uniforms, for everyone? But unlike swimsuits, there isn’t much use for them...” Sara’s eyes widened in surprise.

Yes, this was a different case to the swimsuits. While the uniforms were cute, their appearance was rather different to the general clothes of the spirit folk village, so wearing them as everyday wear would make them stand out. However, Orphia was on board with Latifa’s suggestion. “I think it’s a good idea. I’m sure it’ll be fun,” she said.

“Yes, I agree. We’ll only be showing Haruto, but I don’t think it’s a bad idea.” Alma didn’t seem to be against it, either.

“Don’t you want to show Onii-chan what you look like in a uniform too, Sara? I’m sure he’ll be surprised!” Latifa asked, her smile clearly seeing through Sara.

“Ugh...” When Sara imagined herself wearing a uniform in front of Rio, her cheeks reddened. For some reason, she felt unreasonably embarrassed about it, possibly because it wasn’t her usual wear.

Orphia giggled teasingly. “Fufu, if Sara isn’t into it, we could make it for ourselves and show Haruto without her.”

“Wha — H-Hold it right there! I never said I wouldn’t! I’ll make it, I’ll make it too!” Sara said in a fluster.

Latifa and Vera exchanged glances before giggling. “Fufufu...”

“W-What are you two laughing at?” Sara asked the two of them in a voice squeaking with embarrassment.

“Nothing!” they reacted innocently in sync.

Miharu and Aki smiled while watching their exchange. “Ahaha!”

“So that’s how it is, Miharu. Would you be willing to teach us how to sew once more?” Orphia asked.

“Of course. I’d be happy to,” Miharu agreed easily.

Latifa imagined all of them wearing uniforms and her face broke out into a happy smile. “Ehehe, I wonder if Onii-chan will be happy to see us.”

“Yes, I’m sure he will! Rio really loves you, after all!” Vera declared firmly.

“Yup, I know!” Latifa smiled with the most carefree smile. It was a face that knew fully that she was beloved by Rio.

Latifa sure loves Haruto... Aki thought as she looked at Latifa, feeling a little homesick. She was remembering her stepbrother, Sendo Takahisa. While she didn’t express her affection as directly as Latifa, Aki was aware she also had an unnatural attachment to her brother. That was why when she saw Latifa wholeheartedly adoring Rio, she often ended up thinking about Takahisa. Perhaps she felt empathy in the way she also adored her own stepbrother.

I wonder if Haruto’s noticed Latifa’s feelings?

No, it wasn’t only Latifa — Sara, Orphia, and Alma had the same feelings, too. They were strongly aware of Rio’s presence as a person of the opposite sex.

But Haruto’s surprisingly dull about these things. He seems like a very serious person, but does he have anyone he likes? Maybe someone from this group? Or perhaps Aishia?

Aki looked at the girls around her as she pondered.